[
  {
    "question": "There are ___ seasons in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "The spring season in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "hot and rainy",
      "warm and cozy",
      "dry and sunny",
      "The cold does not come."
    ],
    "answer": "warm and cozy"
  },
  {
    "question": "When the yellow dust blows in Korea, ___ is not a proper preparation for people.",
    "options": [
      "avoiding going out",
      "using an umbrella",
      "closing the windows at home",
      "wearing a mask"
    ],
    "answer": "using an umbrella"
  },
  {
    "question": "The summer season in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "cold yet cozy and warm",
      "dry and humid",
      "snowy",
      "hot and rainy"
    ],
    "answer": "hot and rainy"
  },
  {
    "question": "The autumn season in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "cold yet cozy and warm",
      "hot and rainy",
      "dry and sunny",
      "snowy"
    ],
    "answer": "dry and sunny"
  },
  {
    "question": "___ cannot be seen on the streets in late autumn in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "snow",
      "rain",
      "flowers",
      "fallen leaves"
    ],
    "answer": "fallen leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korea's winter is ___",
    "options": [
      "cold and humid",
      "sunny and dry",
      "cold and dry",
      "cozy and warm"
    ],
    "answer": "cold and dry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on the 2000s, most households in Korea ____ when winter begins.",
    "options": [
      "prepare for spring activities",
      "make kimchi",
      "prepare for water activities",
      "prepare for autumn foliage activities"
    ],
    "answer": "make kimchi"
  },
  {
    "question": "The activity that Koreans enjoy in autumn is ___.",
    "options": [
      "cherry blossom viewing",
      "water play",
      "autumn foliage viewing",
      "skiing"
    ],
    "answer": "autumn foliage viewing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The products mainly sold in summer in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "air conditioners, fans, cold noodles",
      "electric blankets, heaters",
      "autumn foliage items",
      "spring flower items"
    ],
    "answer": "air conditioners, fans, cold noodles"
  },
  {
    "question": "The products mainly sold in winter in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "air conditioners, fans, cold noodles",
      "electric heating mats, heat fans",
      "maple leaf viewing supplies",
      "spring flower viewing supplies"
    ],
    "answer": "electric heating mats, heat fans"
  },
  {
    "question": "The San Gyeong Pyo was compiled by ___.",
    "options": [
      "King Yeongjo",
      "Shin Gyeongjun",
      "Baekdu Daegan",
      "Joseon"
    ],
    "answer": "Shin Gyeongjun"
  },
  {
    "question": "The geographical characteristic of Korea is that ___.",
    "options": [
      "The east is high and the west is low",
      "The west is high and the east is low",
      "The south is high and the north is low",
      "The north is high and the south is low"
    ],
    "answer": "The east is high and the west is low"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ratio of mountains in the total land area of Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "30%",
      "65%",
      "80%",
      "10%"
    ],
    "answer": "65%"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mountain range known as the backbone of the Korean Peninsula is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Baekdu Mountain Range",
      "Taebaek Mountain Range",
      "Jiri Mountain Range",
      "Hallasan Mountain Range"
    ],
    "answer": "Taebaek Mountain Range"
  },
  {
    "question": "A representative mountain located in the Taebaek Mountains is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoraksan and Odaesan",
      "Hallasan and Jirisan",
      "Baektusan and Taebaeksan",
      "Jirisan and Baektusan"
    ],
    "answer": "Seoraksan and Odaesan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The highest mountain in Korea is located in ___.",
    "options": [
      "Jeju Island",
      "Gyeonggi Province",
      "Gangwon Province",
      "Jeolla Province"
    ],
    "answer": "Jeju Island"
  },
  {
    "question": "The area where rice, a staple of Koreans, is not produced in large quantities is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Honam Plain",
      "Naju Plain",
      "Gimpo Plain",
      "Gangwon Plain"
    ],
    "answer": "Gangwon Plain"
  },
  {
    "question": "The region of the Korean Peninsula with a complex coastline and shallow waters is ___.",
    "options": [
      "the southern coast and the western coast",
      "the southern coast and the eastern coast",
      "the western coast and the eastern coast",
      "the eastern coast and the northern coast"
    ],
    "answer": "the southern coast and the western coast"
  },
  {
    "question": "The area where tidal flats are well developed in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "the West Coast and the South Coast",
      "the West Coast and the East Coast",
      "the South Coast and the East Coast",
      "the East Coast and the North Coast"
    ],
    "answer": "the West Coast and the South Coast"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ____ sides of the Korean Peninsula are adjacent to the sea, allowing for various coastal terrains.",
    "options": [
      "east, south, west",
      "east, south, north",
      "west, south, north",
      "east, west, north"
    ],
    "answer": "east, south, west"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year when Seoul became the capital of Korea for the first time is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1392",
      "1592",
      "1292",
      "1492"
    ],
    "answer": "1392"
  },
  {
    "question": "North of the Han River in Seoul is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gangnam",
      "Gangseo",
      "Gangbuk",
      "Gangdong"
    ],
    "answer": "Gangbuk"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the end of December 2013, the population of Seoul is approximately ___ people.",
    "options": [
      "7.14 million",
      "8.14 million",
      "9.14 million",
      "10.14 million"
    ],
    "answer": "10.14 million"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2010s, the region where new towns are continuously being built is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoul",
      "Busan",
      "Daegu",
      "Gyeonggi Province"
    ],
    "answer": "Gyeonggi Province"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is gathered in the metropolitan area.",
    "options": [
      "various companies and schools",
      "farms and ranches",
      "mountains and rivers",
      "beaches and islands"
    ],
    "answer": "various companies and schools"
  },
  {
    "question": "The city where Chinatown is located is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoul",
      "Busan",
      "Incheon",
      "Gwangju"
    ],
    "answer": "Gwangju"
  },
  {
    "question": "Incheon Chinatown preserves the unique culture and customs of the ___",
    "options": [
      "Chinese community's unique culture and customs",
      "Korean unique culture and customs",
      "Japanese unique culture and customs",
      "American unique culture and customs"
    ],
    "answer": "Chinese community's unique culture and customs"
  },
  {
    "question": "The industry developed in Gyeonggi Province is ___.",
    "options": [
      "service industry, manufacturing industry, agriculture",
      "mining, fishing, forestry",
      "tourism, IT industry, manufacturing",
      "finance, real estate, distribution"
    ],
    "answer": "service industry, manufacturing industry, agriculture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Excluding Seoul, the largest city in the metropolitan area is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gwangmyeong",
      "Yongin",
      "Incheon",
      "Suwon"
    ],
    "answer": "Incheon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 20th century, Incheon has played the role of ___.",
    "options": [
      "Agricultural city",
      "Industrial city",
      "Port city",
      "Tourist city"
    ],
    "answer": "Port city"
  },
  {
    "question": "The largest airport in South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gimpo International Airport",
      "Jeju International Airport",
      "Busan International Airport",
      "Incheon International Airport"
    ],
    "answer": "Incheon International Airport"
  },
  {
    "question": "The competition held in Incheon in 2014 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Olympics",
      "Asian Games",
      "World Cup",
      "Universiade"
    ],
    "answer": "Asian Games"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gangwon Province is located in the ___ of the Korean Peninsula.",
    "options": [
      "west",
      "east",
      "south",
      "north"
    ],
    "answer": "east"
  },
  {
    "question": "The eastern region of Gangwon Province is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "Yeongseo Region",
      "Yeongdong Region",
      "Yeongnam Region",
      "Yeongbuk Region"
    ],
    "answer": "Yeongdong Region"
  },
  {
    "question": "The representative cultural heritage of Gangneung is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gyeongpo Pavilion",
      "Ojukheon",
      "Seoraksan",
      "Samcheok Beach"
    ],
    "answer": "Ojukheon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gangwon-do have many facilities of ____.",
    "options": [
      "swimming pools",
      "ski resorts",
      "baseball fields",
      "soccer fields"
    ],
    "answer": "ski resorts"
  },
  {
    "question": "The inconvenience caused by the geographical characteristics of Gangwon-do is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Inconvenience of movement",
      "Difficulty in farming",
      "Communication difficulties",
      "Challenges in commercial activities"
    ],
    "answer": "Inconvenience of movement"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mountain designated as a national park located in Gangwon-do is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoraksan",
      "Hallasan",
      "Jirisan",
      "Bukhansan"
    ],
    "answer": "Seoraksan"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 20th century, the industry that developed significantly in Gangwon-do was ___.",
    "options": [
      "Mining Industry",
      "Agriculture",
      "Fisheries",
      "Manufacturing"
    ],
    "answer": "Mining Industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The event held in Daejeon in 1993 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "World Science Expo",
      "World Cultural Expo",
      "World Economic Forum",
      "World Environmental Conference"
    ],
    "answer": "World Science Expo"
  },
  {
    "question": "The region where many relics of Baekje culture can be observed is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gyeongsangnam-do",
      "Jeollabuk-do",
      "Chungcheongnam-do",
      "Gangwon-do"
    ],
    "answer": "Chungcheongnam-do"
  },
  {
    "question": "The city to which some major government ministries relocated in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Daegu",
      "Gwangju",
      "Sejong",
      "Ulsan"
    ],
    "answer": "Sejong"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mountain located in Chungcheongbuk-do, where a lot of azaleas bloom and many people visit, is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Hallasan",
      "Jirisan",
      "Sobaeksan",
      "Bukhan Mountain"
    ],
    "answer": "Sobaeksan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chungcheongbuk-do does not border ___.",
    "options": [
      "Jeollanam-do",
      "Gangwon-do",
      "Jeollabuk-do",
      "Gyeongsangbuk-do"
    ],
    "answer": "Jeollanam-do"
  },
  {
    "question": "The two cities that served as the capital of Baekje were ___",
    "options": [
      "Seoul and Busan",
      "Gongju and Buyeo",
      "Daejeon and Daegu",
      "Gwangju and Jeonju"
    ],
    "answer": "Gongju and Buyeo"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main crops grown in Chungcheongnam-do are ___.",
    "options": [
      "pear, grape, apple",
      "wheat, soybean, corn",
      "potato, sweet potato, carrot",
      "tomato, cucumber, lettuce"
    ],
    "answer": "pear, grape, apple"
  },
  {
    "question": "The representative large city of the Chungcheong region is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoul",
      "Busan",
      "Daejeon",
      "Incheon"
    ],
    "answer": "Daejeon"
  },
  {
    "question": "The industrial complex that plays an important role in Daejeon is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Automobile Industrial Complex",
      "Science Industrial Complex",
      "Food Industrial Complex",
      "Medical Industrial Complex"
    ],
    "answer": "Science Industrial Complex"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Gyeongsang region is located in the ___ direction of Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Northeast",
      "Northwest",
      "Southwest",
      "Southeast"
    ],
    "answer": "Southeast"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Gyeongsang region includes the following cities ___",
    "options": [
      "Seoul, Incheon, Daejeon",
      "Busan, Daegu, Ulsan",
      "Gwangju, Jeonju, Mokpo",
      "Cheongju, Daejeon, Sejong"
    ],
    "answer": "Busan, Daegu, Ulsan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The island that belongs to the Gyeongsang region is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Jeju Island and Ulleungdo",
      "Dokdo and Ulleungdo",
      "Ganghwa Island and Dokdo",
      "Ulleungdo and Wolmido"
    ],
    "answer": "Dokdo and Ulleungdo"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Gyeongsang region, the ___ industry has developed.",
    "options": [
      "Agriculture",
      "Service industry",
      "Mining",
      "Manufacturing"
    ],
    "answer": "Manufacturing"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Gumi area, the major developed industry is ___.",
    "options": [
      "textile and electronics industry",
      "automobile and shipbuilding industry",
      "agriculture and fisheries",
      "mining and manufacturing"
    ],
    "answer": "textile and electronics industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Pohang and Ulsan, there are representative industries such as ___.",
    "options": [
      "steel mills and shipyards and automobile factories",
      "electronic industry and textile industry",
      "agriculture and fishing",
      "mining and manufacturing"
    ],
    "answer": "steel mills and shipyards and automobile factories"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Busan, ___ is held for international events.",
    "options": [
      "Busan International Film Festival",
      "Busan International Music Festival",
      "Busan International Art Festival",
      "Busan International Literature Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Busan International Film Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gyeongju is the place where many cultural heritages from the ____ period remain.",
    "options": [
      "Goguryeo",
      "Baekje",
      "Silla",
      "Joseon"
    ],
    "answer": "Silla"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Andong region is the place where many cultural heritages from the ____ dynasty remain.",
    "options": [
      "Goguryeo",
      "Baekje",
      "Silla",
      "Joseon"
    ],
    "answer": "Joseon"
  },
  {
    "question": "The event held in Busan in 2002 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Asian Games",
      "World Athletics Championships",
      "World Cup",
      "Hallyu Drama Filming"
    ],
    "answer": "Asian Games"
  },
  {
    "question": "The event held in Daegu in 2013 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Asian Games",
      "World Athletics Championships",
      "Busan International Film Festival",
      "Korean Wave Drama Shoot"
    ],
    "answer": "World Athletics Championships"
  },
  {
    "question": "The location of BIFF Square in Busan is ___",
    "options": [
      "Seomyeon",
      "Nampodong",
      "Haeundae",
      "Gijang"
    ],
    "answer": "Nampodong"
  },
  {
    "question": "The highest mountain in Jeju Island is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Sarak Mountain",
      "Jiri Mountain",
      "Baekdu Mountain",
      "Hallasan"
    ],
    "answer": "Hallasan"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are ____ oreums approximately in Jeju Island.",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "100",
      "300",
      "1000"
    ],
    "answer": "300"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jeju Island has been designated a ____ World Natural Heritage site.",
    "options": [
      "UNESCO",
      "World Health Organization",
      "International Monetary Fund",
      "World Trade Organization"
    ],
    "answer": "UNESCO"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not included in Jeju's volcanic island and lava caves.",
    "options": [
      "Hallasan Natural Reserve",
      "Seongsan Ilchulbong",
      "Geomunoreum",
      "Namsan"
    ],
    "answer": "Namsan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Jeolla region is located in the ___ direction of Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Northwest",
      "Northeast",
      "Southwest",
      "Southeast"
    ],
    "answer": "Southwest"
  },
  {
    "question": "The industries developed in Gwangju Metropolitan City and Gwangyang City are ___.",
    "options": [
      "automobiles and steel",
      "electronics and semiconductors",
      "textiles and clothing",
      "food and beverages"
    ],
    "answer": "automobiles and steel"
  },
  {
    "question": "A factor that did not contribute to the development of the Jeolla region in the 2010s is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Convenience of transportation",
      "Population increase",
      "Entry of companies",
      "Promotion of Jeolla region's specialties"
    ],
    "answer": "Promotion of Jeolla region's specialties"
  },
  {
    "question": "The largest island in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "Ulleungdo",
      "Dokdo",
      "Jeju Island",
      "Geoje Island"
    ],
    "answer": "Jeju Island"
  },
  {
    "question": "The highest mountain in South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Jirisan",
      "Seoraksan",
      "Bukhansan",
      "Hallasan"
    ],
    "answer": "Hallasan"
  },
  {
    "question": "From ancient times, the Jeju region is famous for having many ___ related stories handed down through generations.",
    "options": [
      "wind, stone, women",
      "beach, mountain, cave",
      "sea, tangerine, Dolhareubang",
      "haenyo, stone wall, canola flower"
    ],
    "answer": "wind, stone, women"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Ganghwado mudflat belongs to ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoul",
      "Busan",
      "Incheon",
      "Daegu"
    ],
    "answer": "Incheon"
  },
  {
    "question": "The region with beautiful sandy beaches is ____.",
    "options": [
      "East Coast of Gangwon Province",
      "West Coast of Gyeongsang Province",
      "South Coast of Gyeonggi Province",
      "North Coast of Chungcheong Province"
    ],
    "answer": "East Coast of Gangwon Province"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is a tourist attraction located in Danyang, Chungcheongbuk-do.",
    "options": [
      "Upo Wetland",
      "Myeongdong",
      "Gosudong Cave",
      "Ganghwa Tidal Flat"
    ],
    "answer": "Gosudong Cave"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cheonggyecheon is a tourist attraction in ___.",
    "options": [
      "Busan",
      "Daegu",
      "Seoul",
      "Incheon"
    ],
    "answer": "Seoul"
  },
  {
    "question": "The festival held in Namwon is ___.",
    "options": [
      "World Day",
      "Ceramic Expo",
      "Military Port Festival",
      "Chunhyangje Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Chunhyangje Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "The famous festival held in Icheon is ___.",
    "options": [
      "World Ceramic Expo",
      "World Flower Festival",
      "World Food Festival",
      "World Art Expo"
    ],
    "answer": "World Ceramic Expo"
  },
  {
    "question": "The famous festival held in Goyang is ___.",
    "options": [
      "World Ceramic Expo",
      "World Flower Expo",
      "World Food Festival",
      "World Art Expo"
    ],
    "answer": "World Flower Expo"
  },
  {
    "question": "The festival held in winter at Daegwallyeong and Taebaek Mountain is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Snow Flower Festival",
      "Sunrise Festival",
      "World Ceramic Expo",
      "Mud Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Snow Flower Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "The festival held every year in Buyeo-gun and Gongju-si in Chungcheongnam-do is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Baekje Cultural Festival",
      "World Ceramic Expo",
      "Sunrise Festival",
      "Mud Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Baekje Cultural Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "The festival held in Ulleungdo is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Squid Festival",
      "Hansan Battle Festival",
      "Port Festival",
      "Mask Dance Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Squid Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "The food culture festival held in the Jeolla region is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Namdo Food Culture Grand Festival",
      "Jeonju World Sound Festival",
      "Namwon Chunhyang Festival",
      "Ulleungdo Squid Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Namdo Food Culture Grand Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sunset welcoming festival held in Jeollanam-do takes place in ___.",
    "options": [
      "Beolgyo",
      "Suncheonman",
      "End of the Land Village",
      "Namwon"
    ],
    "answer": "End of the Land Village"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which connection between the seowon and its location is correct? ___",
    "options": [
      "Sosu Seowon - Sangju, Gyeongbuk",
      "Pilam Seowon - Jangseong, Jeonnam",
      "Jawun Seowon - Yeoju, Gyeonggi",
      "Hwayang Seowon - Nonsan, Chungnam"
    ],
    "answer": "Pilam Seowon - Jangseong, Jeonnam"
  },
  {
    "question": "When visiting a traditional cultural site with foreign students, which regional connection is incorrect ___",
    "options": [
      "Jeju - Chilmeoridang Yeongdeunggut",
      "Gangneung - Danoje",
      "Jeonju - Byeolsingut Talnori",
      "Hansan - Mosijjagi"
    ],
    "answer": "Jeonju - Byeolsingut Talnori"
  },
  {
    "question": "An incorrect connections between regions in Korea and their corresponding festivals is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Hwacheon - Sancheoneo Festival",
      "Boryeong - Mud Festival",
      "Buyeo - Seodong Festival",
      "Taebaek - Taebaek Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Buyeo - Seodong Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "An incorrect connection between the site and location is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Gwanghanru - Jinju",
      "Gongsanseong - Gongju",
      "Ojukheon - Gangneung",
      "Manisan Chamseongdan - Ganghwa"
    ],
    "answer": "Gwanghanru - Jinju"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is incorrectly linked with the titles of family members ___",
    "options": [
      "반서갱동(飯西羹東)",
      "어동육서(魚東肉西)",
      "홍동백서(紅東白西)",
      "서두동미(西頭東尾)"
    ],
    "answer": "반서갱동(飯西羹東)"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is listed as relatives in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Aunt, Son-in-law, Uncle",
      "Aunt, Daughter-in-law, Mother-in-law",
      "Aunt, Maternal Aunt, Father-in-law",
      "Aunt, Son-in-law, Maternal Grandmother"
    ],
    "answer": "Aunt, Daughter-in-law, Mother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question": "The phenomena that have arisen due to the rapid increase in smartphone adoption and internet usage in recent Korean society is ___",
    "options": [
      "intensification of environmental pollution",
      "activation of interactive communication",
      "increase in remote workers",
      "active contact with foreigners"
    ],
    "answer": "intensification of environmental pollution"
  },
  {
    "question": "The cause of Korea's low birth rate that is least related to ___",
    "options": [
      "the spread of individualism",
      "excessive spending on child-rearing",
      "the increase of dual-income couples",
      "the introduction of telecommuting"
    ],
    "answer": "the introduction of telecommuting"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a national holiday in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "March 1st Movement Day",
      "Memorial Day",
      "Constitution Day",
      "Hangul Day"
    ],
    "answer": "Memorial Day"
  },
  {
    "question": "The statements about kinship degrees that ____ is correct.",
    "options": [
      "Younger brother is 1 degree.",
      "Grandfather is 2 degrees.",
      "Great-uncle is 3 degrees.",
      "Aunt's son is 5 degrees."
    ],
    "answer": "Grandfather is 2 degrees."
  },
  {
    "question": "The term South Korea is primarily used ___.",
    "options": [
      "when distinguishing from North Korea",
      "in international conferences",
      "in English-speaking countries",
      "when using Chinese characters"
    ],
    "answer": "when distinguishing from North Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year when the name of the country 'Republic of Korea' was first used is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1945",
      "1948",
      "1950",
      "1953"
    ],
    "answer": "1948"
  },
  {
    "question": "The name of the national flag of South Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "Tricolor flag",
      "Taegeukgi",
      "Star flag",
      "Dancheong flag"
    ],
    "answer": "Taegeukgi"
  },
  {
    "question": "The element of the Taegukgi that is not correct is ___.",
    "options": [
      "white background",
      "red and blue Taeguk pattern",
      "black four trigrams at the corners",
      "yellow star in the center"
    ],
    "answer": "yellow star in the center"
  },
  {
    "question": "The white background of the Taegeukgi signifies ____ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "a love for brightness, purity, and peace",
      "hope and future",
      "freedom and independence",
      "peace and harmony"
    ],
    "answer": "a love for brightness, purity, and peace"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the taeguk symbol of the national flag, the merging of red and blue represents ___.",
    "options": [
      "harmonious universe",
      "peace and unity",
      "harmony of nature",
      "brightness and purity"
    ],
    "answer": "harmonious universe"
  },
  {
    "question": "The value emphasized by the Taegukgi is ___",
    "options": [
      "Peace and harmony",
      "Freedom and independence",
      "Hope and future",
      "Brightness and purity"
    ],
    "answer": "Peace and harmony"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the day when the national flag is usually hung at home is ___.",
    "options": [
      "national holidays or national commemorative days",
      "birthdays or wedding anniversaries",
      "Christmas or Lunar New Year",
      "Children's Day or Chuseok"
    ],
    "answer": "national holidays or national commemorative days"
  },
  {
    "question": "Regarding the national anthem of South Korea, it is ___.",
    "options": [
      "the People's Song",
      "the Patriotic Song",
      "the Unification Song",
      "the Democratic Song"
    ],
    "answer": "the Patriotic Song"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Korean national anthem consists of a total of ____ verses.",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "When holding an important event in Korea, saluting is ___.",
    "options": [
      "national anthem",
      "National Assembly",
      "Taegeukgi",
      "people"
    ],
    "answer": "Taegeukgi"
  },
  {
    "question": "The oath taken during important events in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Oath of the People",
      "Oath of the Nation",
      "Oath to the Taegeukgi",
      "Oath to the Constitution"
    ],
    "answer": "Oath to the Taegeukgi"
  },
  {
    "question": "When pledging allegiance to the Taegeukgi, it is correct to place your hand on ___.",
    "options": [
      "right chest",
      "left chest",
      "above the head",
      "both shoulders"
    ],
    "answer": "left chest"
  },
  {
    "question": "The national anthem began to be used in Korea about ___.",
    "options": [
      "50 years ago",
      "100 years ago",
      "150 years ago",
      "200 years ago"
    ],
    "answer": "100 years ago"
  },
  {
    "question": "The meaning of the national anthem is ___",
    "options": [
      "A song that protects the country",
      "A song that loves the country",
      "A song for the country",
      "A song that creates the country"
    ],
    "answer": "A song that loves the country"
  },
  {
    "question": "When important national events are held in Korea, ___ is done.",
    "options": [
      "greeting",
      "applause",
      "salute",
      "celebration"
    ],
    "answer": "salute"
  },
  {
    "question": "Except for important national events, the verse mainly sung of the national anthem is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1st verse",
      "2nd verse",
      "3rd verse",
      "4th verse"
    ],
    "answer": "1st verse"
  },
  {
    "question": "The composer of the national anthem is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Ahn Ik-tae",
      "Yoon Dong-ju",
      "Kim So-wol",
      "Lee Hyo-seok"
    ],
    "answer": "Ahn Ik-tae"
  },
  {
    "question": "The national flower that symbolizes South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Rose",
      "Tulip",
      "Hibiscus",
      "Cherry Blossom"
    ],
    "answer": "Hibiscus"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the hibiscus primarily symbolizes ___.",
    "options": [
      "a flower symbolizing beauty",
      "a flower symbolizing happiness",
      "a flower symbolizing the country",
      "a flower symbolizing peace"
    ],
    "answer": "a flower symbolizing the country"
  },
  {
    "question": "The shape of the hibiscus flower in full bloom is used in the ____.",
    "options": [
      "National Anthem of the Republic of Korea",
      "National Flag of the Republic of Korea",
      "National Song of the Republic of Korea",
      "Constitution of the Republic of Korea"
    ],
    "answer": "National Anthem of the Republic of Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "The rose of Sharon has been loved as the symbol flower of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Japan",
      "China",
      "United States",
      "Korea"
    ],
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "The shape of the fully blossomed hibiscus flower is used to symbolize the ____.",
    "options": [
      "National Anthem of the Republic of Korea",
      "National Flag of the Republic of Korea",
      "Government of the Republic of Korea",
      "Constitution of the Republic of Korea"
    ],
    "answer": "Government of the Republic of Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "The rose of Sharon is the flower that symbolizes ___",
    "options": [
      "Japan",
      "China",
      "the United States",
      "South Korea"
    ],
    "answer": "South Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the 21st century, Hangul was created ____ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "100 years ago",
      "600 years ago",
      "2000 years ago",
      "Exists since BC"
    ],
    "answer": "600 years ago"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hangul is composed of ___ in the Korean language.",
    "options": [
      "10 consonants, 14 vowels",
      "14 consonants, 10 vowels",
      "12 consonants, 12 vowels",
      "15 consonants, 9 vowels"
    ],
    "answer": "14 consonants, 10 vowels"
  },
  {
    "question": "The vowels of Hangul were created by combining elements of heaven, earth, ___.",
    "options": [
      "wind",
      "fire",
      "human",
      "water"
    ],
    "answer": "human"
  },
  {
    "question": "The total number of consonants and vowels in Hangul is ___.",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "22",
      "24",
      "26"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "After the creation of Hangul, illiteracy in Korea ___",
    "options": [
      "increased",
      "decreased",
      "retreated",
      "remained unchanged"
    ],
    "answer": "decreased"
  },
  {
    "question": "The award created by UNESCO to commemorate the achievements of Hangul is ___.",
    "options": [
      "King Sejong Award",
      "Hangul Award",
      "Sejong Award",
      "UNESCO Award"
    ],
    "answer": "King Sejong Award"
  },
  {
    "question": "The name of the mobile phone keypad that can compose Hangul is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Cheonjiin",
      "Naratgeul",
      "Sejong",
      "Hunminjeongeum"
    ],
    "answer": "Cheonjiin"
  },
  {
    "question": "The person who created Hangul is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Taejo",
      "Sejong",
      "Yejong",
      "Jeongjo"
    ],
    "answer": "Sejong"
  },
  {
    "question": "The influence of Hangul on Korean culture after it was created is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Culture has developed",
      "Culture has declined",
      "There has been little change in culture",
      "Culture has become diverse"
    ],
    "answer": "Culture has developed"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2020, the age range for marriage in Korea is generally ___",
    "options": [
      "getting lower",
      "unchanged",
      "getting higher",
      "changing irregularly"
    ],
    "answer": "getting higher"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 1980s, a typical family in Korea usually has ____ children.",
    "options": [
      "1-2",
      "3-5",
      "6-8",
      "9 or more"
    ],
    "answer": "3-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 1980s in Korea, it was common for children who lived with their parents even after marriage to be ___.",
    "options": [
      "first son",
      "second son",
      "first daughter",
      "second daughter"
    ],
    "answer": "first son"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 1980s In Korea, the family structures of ____ were commonly seen.",
    "options": [
      "nuclear family",
      "extended family",
      "single-family",
      "blended family"
    ],
    "answer": "extended family"
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on the 2010s, the main family structure in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "nuclear family",
      "extended family",
      "single-person household",
      "households with only couples"
    ],
    "answer": "nuclear family"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2010s, the family type that is increasing in Korean society is ___.",
    "options": [
      "extended family",
      "nuclear family",
      "single-person household",
      "households with only a couple"
    ],
    "answer": "single-person household"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the expression mainly used for a man getting married is ___.",
    "options": [
      "getting married (to a husband)",
      "getting married (to a wife)",
      "getting married (in general)",
      "leaving"
    ],
    "answer": "getting married (to a wife)"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The term used by a child to refer to their mother's siblings is ___.",
    "options": [
      "imo",
      "oesamchon",
      "gomo",
      "samchon"
    ],
    "answer": "oesamchon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The term used by a child to address their father's sister is ___.",
    "options": [
      "imo",
      "oesamchon",
      "gomo",
      "samchon"
    ],
    "answer": "gomo"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the term that a child uses to call their father's brother is ___.",
    "options": [
      "imo",
      "oesamchon",
      "gomo",
      "samchon"
    ],
    "answer": "samchon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the expression \"sikgu\" means ___.",
    "options": [
      "a very close and intimate relationship",
      "friend",
      "colleague",
      "people who eat together at one table"
    ],
    "answer": "people who eat together at one table"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the way couples address each other is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Honey, dear",
      "Dad, mom",
      "Older brother, older sister",
      "Call each other's names"
    ],
    "answer": "Honey, dear"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the way a husband addresses his wife's parents is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Father, mother",
      "Father-in-law, mother-in-law",
      "Dad, mother",
      "Grandfather, grandmother"
    ],
    "answer": "Father-in-law, mother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, parents-in-law call a daughter-in-law who has not yet given birth to a child ___.",
    "options": [
      "eomeom-a",
      "(sae)aga",
      "daughter-in-law",
      "son's wife"
    ],
    "answer": "(sae)aga"
  },
  {
    "question": "After giving birth In Korea, the parents-in-law call the daughter-in-law ___.",
    "options": [
      "daughter-in-law",
      "(sae)aga",
      "eomeom-a",
      "son's wife"
    ],
    "answer": "eomeom-a"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the son-in-law's surname is \"Kim,\" the wife’s parents call their son-in-law ___",
    "options": [
      "Kim adeul",
      "Kim adeulnim",
      "Kim seobang",
      "Kim sawi"
    ],
    "answer": "Kim seobang"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, ___ is not used by a couple to refer to each other after having a child.",
    "options": [
      "Honey",
      "You",
      "xx Dad, xx Mom",
      "Mom, Dad"
    ],
    "answer": "Mom, Dad"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the term used by a wife to address her husband’s parents is ___.",
    "options": [
      "abeonim, eomeonim",
      "jang-in-eoleun, jangmonim",
      "appa, eomma",
      "hal-abeoji, halmeoni"
    ],
    "answer": "abeonim, eomeonim"
  },
  {
    "question": "The wife calls the husband's older sister ___.",
    "options": [
      "Miss",
      "Older Brother",
      "Older Brother-in-law",
      "Young Master"
    ],
    "answer": "Older Brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, a wife refers to her husband's married younger brother as ___.",
    "options": [
      "Ajubeonim",
      "Adeunim",
      "Seobangnim",
      "Hyeongnim"
    ],
    "answer": "Seobangnim"
  },
  {
    "question": "The husband calls the wife's older brother ___.",
    "options": [
      "brother-in-law",
      "sister-in-law",
      "older brother",
      "brother-in-law"
    ],
    "answer": "older brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, family and kinship relationships are indicated with ___.",
    "options": [
      "Degree of kinship",
      "Generation",
      "Class",
      "Grade"
    ],
    "answer": "Degree of kinship"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parents and children are ____ in Korean.",
    "options": [
      "1st degree",
      "2nd degree",
      "3rd degree",
      "4th degree"
    ],
    "answer": "1st degree"
  },
  {
    "question": "When you get married and have a child, your younger brother and your child are ___ cousins in Korean.",
    "options": [
      "1st",
      "2nd",
      "3rd",
      "4th"
    ],
    "answer": "3rd"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your younger brother's child and your child are ___ cousins in Korean.",
    "options": [
      "1st",
      "2nd",
      "3rd",
      "4th"
    ],
    "answer": "4th"
  },
  {
    "question": "The children born from the siblings of a husband or wife are called ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "brothers",
      "cousins",
      "colleagues",
      "friends"
    ],
    "answer": "cousins"
  },
  {
    "question": "The relationship of my child to my wife's male sibling's child is called ____.",
    "options": [
      "chinsachon",
      "gojongsachon",
      "oesachon",
      "ijongsachon"
    ],
    "answer": "oesachon"
  },
  {
    "question": "The relationship of my child and my husband's female sibling's child is called ____.",
    "options": [
      "chinsachon",
      "gojongsachon",
      "oesachon",
      "ijongsachon"
    ],
    "answer": "gojongsachon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on the 2010s, the age at which most people retire from work in South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "around 40 years old",
      "around 55 to 60 years old",
      "around 65 to 70 years old",
      "over 70 years old"
    ],
    "answer": "around 55 to 60 years old"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the age at which it is possible to work is ___.",
    "options": [
      "10 years old",
      "12 years old",
      "15 years old",
      "18 years old"
    ],
    "answer": "15 years old"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2020, a popular job in Korean society is ___.",
    "options": [
      "doctor",
      "lawyer",
      "public servant",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "doctor"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea compared to the early 20th century, ____ has led to a reduction in the gap in economic activity rates between women and men.",
    "options": [
      "Increase in women's participation in society",
      "Decrease in men's participation in society",
      "Increase in population",
      "Decrease in economic activity"
    ],
    "answer": "Increase in women's participation in society"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2010s, the company that many people want to work for in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "small and medium enterprises",
      "startups",
      "large corporations",
      "foreign companies"
    ],
    "answer": "large corporations"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most people working in Korea in the 1980s were ___.",
    "options": [
      "women",
      "men",
      "children",
      "elderly"
    ],
    "answer": "men"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since 2010, the reason why the male ratio in South Korea was higher and then the male-female ratio became similar is ___.",
    "options": [
      "elementary school enrollment rate",
      "middle school enrollment rate",
      "high school enrollment rate",
      "university enrollment rate"
    ],
    "answer": "university enrollment rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Many types of couples in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "dual-income couples",
      "stay-at-home couples",
      "stay-at-home couples",
      "couples where neither works"
    ],
    "answer": "dual-income couples"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is particularly emphasized by Korean people in the workplace compared to other countries.",
    "options": [
      "Relationships",
      "Work Performance",
      "Work Efficiency",
      "Task Distribution"
    ],
    "answer": "Relationships"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason why many married women quit their jobs is ___",
    "options": [
      "due to childbirth and parenting",
      "due to workplace relationships",
      "due to work pressure in the workplace",
      "due to performance pressure in the workplace"
    ],
    "answer": "due to childbirth and parenting"
  },
  {
    "question": "The difficulties that women who want to return to work after raising their children experience are ___.",
    "options": [
      "difficulty in re-employment",
      "difficulty in child-rearing",
      "difficulty in workplace relationships",
      "difficulty in work burdens"
    ],
    "answer": "difficulty in re-employment"
  },
  {
    "question": "The person to whom formal language is used in a Korean workplace is ___",
    "options": [
      "only to superiors",
      "to both colleagues and superiors",
      "only to the highest-ranking person",
      "to older people"
    ],
    "answer": "to both colleagues and superiors"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the places that are open almost every day except for holidays are ___.",
    "options": [
      "convenience store",
      "library",
      "community service center",
      "gym"
    ],
    "answer": "convenience store"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean workplaces, the main way to address each other is ___.",
    "options": [
      "name",
      "position",
      "title",
      "nickname"
    ],
    "answer": "position"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean workplaces, colleagues who are close to each other often call each other ____ create a close relationship.",
    "options": [
      "by position",
      "by title",
      "by 'hyeongnim' or 'eonni', or by name",
      "by nickname"
    ],
    "answer": "by 'hyeongnim' or 'eonni', or by name"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean workplaces, creating small gatherings primarily for enjoyment is ___.",
    "options": [
      "hobbies",
      "work discussions",
      "economic activities",
      "academic research"
    ],
    "answer": "hobbies"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korean office workers generally take vacation during ___.",
    "options": [
      "January",
      "April",
      "Late July or early August",
      "December"
    ],
    "answer": "Late July or early August"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is known that Koreans mainly go to ___ during the summer vacation season.",
    "options": [
      "mountains",
      "beaches or valleys",
      "cities",
      "shopping malls"
    ],
    "answer": "beaches or valleys"
  },
  {
    "question": "The usual working hours in Korean government offices or companies are ___.",
    "options": [
      "from 8 AM to 5 PM",
      "from 9 AM to 6 PM",
      "from 10 AM to 7 PM",
      "from 11 AM to 8 PM"
    ],
    "answer": "from 9 AM to 6 PM"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean government offices or companies, the usual time for lunch break is ___.",
    "options": [
      "11 o'clock",
      "12 o'clock",
      "1 o'clock",
      "2 o'clock"
    ],
    "answer": "12 o'clock"
  },
  {
    "question": "In South Korea, public institutions or companies typically work for ___ a day.",
    "options": [
      "6 hours",
      "7 hours",
      "8 hours",
      "9 hours"
    ],
    "answer": "8 hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "The work system applied in most Korean workplaces is ___.",
    "options": [
      "7-day work week",
      "6-day work week",
      "5-day work week",
      "4-day work week"
    ],
    "answer": "5-day work week"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dining together after work among employees in Korea is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "exercise",
      "company dinner",
      "watching a movie",
      "shopping"
    ],
    "answer": "company dinner"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main reason for having a gathering in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "stress relief and celebration",
      "project discussion",
      "strengthening communication with family",
      "exercise and health promotion"
    ],
    "answer": "stress relief and celebration"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a Korean company dinner, the main activity employees engage in is ___.",
    "options": [
      "singing",
      "watching a movie",
      "eating and drinking alcohol",
      "playing games"
    ],
    "answer": "eating and drinking alcohol"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a Korean city, a place that operates 24 hours a day is ___.",
    "options": [
      "convenience store",
      "library",
      "subway station",
      "academy"
    ],
    "answer": "convenience store"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main mode of transportation used for moving within the city in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "city bus, subway, taxi",
      "bicycle, taxi, subway",
      "city bus, bicycle, taxi",
      "subway, taxi, airplane"
    ],
    "answer": "city bus, subway, taxi"
  },
  {
    "question": "The subway lines operating in Seoul include ___.",
    "options": [
      "Lines 1~9, Bundang Line, Shinbundang Line",
      "Lines 1~5, Bundang Line, Shinbundang Line",
      "Lines 1~10, Bundang Line, Sinlim Line",
      "Lines 1~9, Bundang Line, Sindorim Line"
    ],
    "answer": "Lines 1~9, Bundang Line, Shinbundang Line"
  },
  {
    "question": "The subway is a mode of transportation mainly used in ____.",
    "options": [
      "large cities",
      "rural areas",
      "walking paths",
      "beaches"
    ],
    "answer": "large cities"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main mode of transportation used when traveling long distances outside the city is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Taxi",
      "Bicycle",
      "Intercity bus, express bus, train",
      "Subway"
    ],
    "answer": "Intercity bus, express bus, train"
  },
  {
    "question": "The place where people take the city bus is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "bus stop",
      "subway station",
      "taxi stand",
      "airport terminal"
    ],
    "answer": "bus stop"
  },
  {
    "question": "One way to know the arrival time of the city bus in advance in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "cell phone and the bus stop's electronic display",
      "newspaper",
      "radio",
      "television"
    ],
    "answer": "cell phone and the bus stop's electronic display"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the transportation method that cannot be used with a transportation card is ___.",
    "options": [
      "subway",
      "city bus",
      "taxi",
      "KTX"
    ],
    "answer": "KTX"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ cannot be used as a transportation card in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Credit Card",
      "Mobile Phone",
      "Debit Card",
      "ID Card"
    ],
    "answer": "ID Card"
  },
  {
    "question": "The model taxi has a characteristic of providing ___.",
    "options": [
      "Cheaper fare than regular taxis",
      "Higher service than regular taxis",
      "Slower speed than regular taxis",
      "Smaller vehicle size than regular taxis"
    ],
    "answer": "Higher service than regular taxis"
  },
  {
    "question": "The characteristic of KTX is ___.",
    "options": [
      "the slowest train",
      "the cheapest fare",
      "the fastest train",
      "the train that operates the latest"
    ],
    "answer": "the fastest train"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main payment method used when using public transportation in South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Cash",
      "Transportation Card",
      "Credit Card",
      "Check Card"
    ],
    "answer": "Transportation Card"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most convenient way to use intercity buses, express buses, and trains in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "to book in advance through the internet",
      "to buy on-site immediately",
      "to book by phone",
      "to book by mail"
    ],
    "answer": "to book in advance through the internet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korea's types of trains include KTX, Saemaul-ho, Mugunghwa-ho, ___.",
    "options": [
      "Nuriro-ho",
      "Kolban",
      "Mobeom Taxi",
      "General Taxi"
    ],
    "answer": "Nuriro-ho"
  },
  {
    "question": "When using public transportation in Korea, you mainly use ___",
    "options": [
      "Cash",
      "Transportation card",
      "Credit card",
      "Debit card"
    ],
    "answer": "Transportation card"
  },
  {
    "question": "By using the transfer system in Korea, you can receive ___ benefits.",
    "options": [
      "fare discount",
      "priority boarding",
      "weekly free usage",
      "meal provision"
    ],
    "answer": "fare discount"
  },
  {
    "question": "The description about transferring public transportation that ____ is correct in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "There is no limit on the number of times.",
      "It must be used immediately.",
      "It can be used up to once.",
      "It must be used within a certain time."
    ],
    "answer": "It must be used within a certain time."
  },
  {
    "question": "To use the transfer system in Korea, ___.",
    "options": [
      "Apply on the website",
      "Tap the card on the terminal",
      "Tell the driver directly",
      "Receive a special transfer card"
    ],
    "answer": "Tap the card on the terminal"
  },
  {
    "question": "The place that delivers mail, luggage, goods, etc. to the desired location in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Post Office",
      "Wireless Communication Company",
      "Bank",
      "Police Department"
    ],
    "answer": "Post Office"
  },
  {
    "question": "KBS secures its operating costs ___.",
    "options": [
      "advertising",
      "TV license fee",
      "donations",
      "government support funds"
    ],
    "answer": "TV license fee"
  },
  {
    "question": "A place where newspapers cannot be purchased is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "subway station",
      "bus stop",
      "convenience store",
      "large mart"
    ],
    "answer": "large mart"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year when the ‘Gangnam Style’ music video made it into the Guinness Book is ___.",
    "options": [
      "2010",
      "2011",
      "2012",
      "2013"
    ],
    "answer": "2012"
  },
  {
    "question": "South Korea's public TV channels include ___.",
    "options": [
      "KBS, MBC, SBS, EBS",
      "KBS, MBC, SBS, TBS",
      "KBS, MBC, EBS, TBS",
      "MBC, SBS, EBS, TBS"
    ],
    "answer": "KBS, MBC, SBS, EBS"
  },
  {
    "question": "EBS mainly broadcasts ___ types of programs.",
    "options": [
      "education",
      "entertainment",
      "sports",
      "news"
    ],
    "answer": "education"
  },
  {
    "question": "The video sharing site that helped the music video 'Gangnam Style' gain worldwide attention is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Naver",
      "Daum",
      "YouTube",
      "Facebook"
    ],
    "answer": "YouTube"
  },
  {
    "question": "Joseon Ilbo, JoongAng Ilbo, Dong-A Ilbo, Hankook Ilbo, Hankyoreh, and Kyunghyang Sinmun are ____ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "General Newspapers",
      "Sports/Economic Newspapers",
      "Local/Regional Newspapers",
      "Internet Newspapers"
    ],
    "answer": "General Newspapers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Busan Ilbo, Gwangju Ilbo, Chungcheong Daily, etc. are ___ published in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "general newspapers",
      "sports/economic newspapers",
      "local/regional newspapers",
      "internet newspapers"
    ],
    "answer": "local/regional newspapers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Public broadcasting is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Broadcasting operated by public institutions",
      "Broadcasting operated by individuals",
      "Broadcasting operated by the state",
      "Broadcasting operated by the community"
    ],
    "answer": "Broadcasting operated by public institutions"
  },
  {
    "question": "The broadcasting company that is not a public channel is ___.",
    "options": [
      "KBS",
      "EBS",
      "MBC",
      "JTBC"
    ],
    "answer": "JTBC"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2020, one of the most used portal sites in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "Daum",
      "Naver",
      "Nate",
      "Yahoo"
    ],
    "answer": "Naver"
  },
  {
    "question": "The singer of Gangnam Style is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Psy",
      "IU",
      "BTS",
      "BLACKPINK"
    ],
    "answer": "Psy"
  },
  {
    "question": "The one that is not used as SNS in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "KakaoTalk",
      "Twitter",
      "Facebook",
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the main activity done through blogs is ___.",
    "options": [
      "to express topics of personal interest.",
      "to play online games.",
      "to watch movies.",
      "to listen to music."
    ],
    "answer": "to express topics of personal interest."
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Social insurance is a system that citizens should join to prepare for future risks ___.",
    "options": [
      "to prepare for future risks",
      "to prepare for current risks",
      "to prepare for past risks",
      "to seize future opportunities"
    ],
    "answer": "to prepare for future risks"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the ministry that provides information about the minimum living expenses is ___.",
    "options": [
      "National Health Insurance Corporation",
      "Labor Welfare Corporation",
      "Ministry of Gender Equality and Family",
      "Ministry of Health and Welfare"
    ],
    "answer": "Ministry of Health and Welfare"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the problems caused by urban population growth in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "housing shortage and rising house prices",
      "food shortage",
      "lack of educational opportunities",
      "decreased life expectancy"
    ],
    "answer": "housing shortage and rising house prices"
  },
  {
    "question": "The key industry in Korea in the 1900s was ___.",
    "options": [
      "Agriculture",
      "Manufacturing",
      "Service",
      "IT"
    ],
    "answer": "Agriculture"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2010s, the proportion of the population living in rural areas in South Korea is ___ of the total population.",
    "options": [
      "5%",
      "10%",
      "20%",
      "30%"
    ],
    "answer": "10%"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the place where the relationships among residents are more likely to be intimate is ___",
    "options": [
      "rural areas",
      "urban areas",
      "both are the same",
      "lack of information"
    ],
    "answer": "rural areas"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a phenomenon that started in Korea after the 2010s.",
    "options": [
      "Increase in population returning to farming",
      "Decrease in rural population",
      "Increase in urban population",
      "Increase in birth rate"
    ],
    "answer": "Increase in birth rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "The period during which South Korea's industrialization progressed rapidly is ___.",
    "options": [
      "the 1950s",
      "the 1960s",
      "the 1970s",
      "the 1980s"
    ],
    "answer": "the 1960s"
  },
  {
    "question": "The phenomenon that appeared during the process of industrialization is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Urbanization",
      "Agriculturalization",
      "Forestry",
      "Politicalization"
    ],
    "answer": "Urbanization"
  },
  {
    "question": "The current urban population ratio in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "70%",
      "80%",
      "90%",
      "100%"
    ],
    "answer": "90%"
  },
  {
    "question": "The region where the population is most concentrated in South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoul, Gyeonggi",
      "Busan, Gyeongnam",
      "Daegu, Gyeongbuk",
      "Gwangju, Jeonnam"
    ],
    "answer": "Seoul, Gyeonggi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Compared to university hospitals, local clinics are mainly places to go ___.",
    "options": [
      "when there are relatively mild symptoms",
      "when detailed examinations are needed",
      "when vaccinations are needed",
      "when dental treatment is needed"
    ],
    "answer": "when there are relatively mild symptoms"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the health insurance card is issued by ___.",
    "options": [
      "National Health Insurance Service",
      "hospital",
      "pharmacy",
      "health center"
    ],
    "answer": "National Health Insurance Service"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, University hospitals are primarily places to go when ___",
    "options": [
      "there are relatively mild symptoms",
      "detailed examinations are needed",
      "vaccinations are required",
      "dental treatment is needed"
    ],
    "answer": "detailed examinations are needed"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the health center is operated by ___.",
    "options": [
      "the state",
      "individuals",
      "hospitals",
      "pharmacies"
    ],
    "answer": "the state"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, ____ is designated for each emergency situation.",
    "options": [
      "report number",
      "report location",
      "report personnel",
      "report time"
    ],
    "answer": "report number"
  },
  {
    "question": "Koreans often consider the number ___ to be an ominous number.",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the reason why the 4th of every month is designated as Safety Inspection Day is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1986",
      "1996",
      "2006",
      "2016"
    ],
    "answer": "1996"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, ___ is the day for safety inspections every month.",
    "options": [
      "1st",
      "2nd",
      "3rd",
      "4th"
    ],
    "answer": "4th"
  },
  {
    "question": "The documents required to apply for support for pregnancy and childbirth medical expenses are ___.",
    "options": [
      "Pregnancy Confirmation Certificate",
      "Birth Confirmation Certificate",
      "Medical Expense Support Application Form",
      "Pregnancy Diagnosis Certificate"
    ],
    "answer": "Pregnancy Confirmation Certificate"
  },
  {
    "question": "The total fertility rate refers ___",
    "options": [
      "the number of children born per enrolled woman",
      "the number of pregnancies per enrolled woman",
      "the number of unmarried mothers per enrolled woman",
      "the number of unmarried fathers per enrolled woman"
    ],
    "answer": "the number of children born per enrolled woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "The maternity and childbirth support fund can be used at ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "designated care institutions",
      "all hospitals",
      "designated pharmacies",
      "all pharmacies"
    ],
    "answer": "designated care institutions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Childcare and education for infants and toddlers in Korea is provided in ___.",
    "options": [
      "daycare centers",
      "elementary schools",
      "middle schools",
      "high schools"
    ],
    "answer": "daycare centers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Daycare centers are generally ___ operated in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "from 7:30 AM to 7:30 PM on weekdays",
      "from 9:00 AM to 2:00 PM on weekdays",
      "from 7:00 AM to 8:00 PM on weekends",
      "from 8:00 AM to 6:00 PM on weekends"
    ],
    "answer": "from 7:30 AM to 7:30 PM on weekdays"
  },
  {
    "question": "To send a child to a national or public educational institution in Korea, one must go through ___ process.",
    "options": [
      "immediate registration",
      "registration right after application",
      "long wait after application",
      "registration without application"
    ],
    "answer": "long wait after application"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the difficulty in sending children to national and public educational institutions is ___",
    "options": [
      "You have to wait a long time after applying",
      "The application itself is difficult",
      "Tuition fees are expensive",
      "The quality of education is low"
    ],
    "answer": "You have to wait a long time after applying"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is generally understood that national schools are established and operated by ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "individual",
      "private organization",
      "local government",
      "state (central government)"
    ],
    "answer": "state (central government)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Public schools are established and operated by ___",
    "options": [
      "Individuals",
      "Private organizations",
      "Local governments",
      "The state (central government)"
    ],
    "answer": "Local governments"
  },
  {
    "question": "Private schools are established and operated by ___",
    "options": [
      "individuals or private organizations",
      "local governments",
      "the state (central government)",
      "educational offices"
    ],
    "answer": "individuals or private organizations"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main role of the education office is ___.",
    "options": [
      "development of curriculum",
      "placement of teachers",
      "establishment of schools",
      "managing education in each region"
    ],
    "answer": "managing education in each region"
  },
  {
    "question": "The case of attending a private elementary school is mainly decided by ___.",
    "options": [
      "academic performance",
      "lottery",
      "interview",
      "school discretion"
    ],
    "answer": "lottery"
  },
  {
    "question": "What parents of elementary school students in Korea must check every day is ___.",
    "options": [
      "notification book",
      "school website",
      "school newsletter",
      "school schedule"
    ],
    "answer": "notification book"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2010s, there are the most ___ universities in South Korea.",
    "options": [
      "2-year",
      "3-year",
      "4-year",
      "5-year"
    ],
    "answer": "4-year"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korean universities have established ___ to reduce the burden of tuition fees.",
    "options": [
      "scholarship system",
      "discount system",
      "free education system",
      "educational support fund system"
    ],
    "answer": "scholarship system"
  },
  {
    "question": "The educational institution responsible for elementary education in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Middle School",
      "High School",
      "Elementary School",
      "University"
    ],
    "answer": "Elementary School"
  },
  {
    "question": "The duration of middle school education in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "6 years",
      "3 years",
      "4 years",
      "2 years"
    ],
    "answer": "3 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "The compulsory education period in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "6 years",
      "9 years",
      "12 years",
      "15 years"
    ],
    "answer": "9 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "The second semester in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "March~August",
      "September~February of the next year",
      "January~June",
      "July~December"
    ],
    "answer": "September~February of the next year"
  },
  {
    "question": "The schools that must provide compulsory education in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "Elementary school and middle school",
      "Middle school and high school",
      "Elementary school and high school",
      "Elementary school, middle school, and high school"
    ],
    "answer": "Elementary school and middle school"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the factor that the education office considers when assigning students to national and public elementary schools is ___.",
    "options": [
      "student's grades",
      "student's behavior",
      "distance between home and school",
      "student's preferences"
    ],
    "answer": "distance between home and school"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Specialized high schools emphasize vocational education, which means ___",
    "options": [
      "science education",
      "art education",
      "vocational education",
      "physical education"
    ],
    "answer": "vocational education"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the entity that sends the home communication is ___.",
    "options": [
      "music teacher",
      "homeroom teacher",
      "school office",
      "parent committee"
    ],
    "answer": "homeroom teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "The content recorded in the notification book is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "school supplies, homework, etc.",
      "school menu",
      "school schedule",
      "information about school events"
    ],
    "answer": "school supplies, homework, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1980, the college enrollment rate in Korea was ___.",
    "options": [
      "27%",
      "70%",
      "79%",
      "54%"
    ],
    "answer": "27%"
  },
  {
    "question": "The college enrollment rate in South Korea in 2010 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "27%",
      "70%",
      "79%",
      "54%"
    ],
    "answer": "79%"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are ___ in Korea's higher education institutions.",
    "options": [
      "universities and graduate schools",
      "high schools and universities",
      "middle schools and high schools",
      "elementary schools and middle schools"
    ],
    "answer": "universities and graduate schools"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not included in the special-purpose high schools in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Science High School",
      "Foreign Language High School",
      "Art High School",
      "Science Focus High School"
    ],
    "answer": "Science Focus High School"
  },
  {
    "question": "The exam commonly taken to enter university in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "TOEIC",
      "TOEFL",
      "Suneung",
      "SAT"
    ],
    "answer": "Suneung"
  },
  {
    "question": "The College Scholastic Ability Test (CSAT) is held every year in Korea in ___.",
    "options": [
      "October",
      "November",
      "December",
      "January"
    ],
    "answer": "November"
  },
  {
    "question": "The process that one goes through for college admission besides the CSAT is ___.",
    "options": [
      "interviews, essays, etc.",
      "TOEIC, TOEFL, etc.",
      "GRE, GMAT, etc.",
      "IELTS, SAT, etc."
    ],
    "answer": "interviews, essays, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2014, the college enrollment rate in South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "about 60%",
      "about 70%",
      "about 80%",
      "about 90%"
    ],
    "answer": "about 70%"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, high school corresponds to ___.",
    "options": [
      "mandatory education",
      "optional education",
      "special education",
      "universal education"
    ],
    "answer": "optional education"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main purpose of the Suneung is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "to confirm the ability to study at a university",
      "for high school graduation",
      "to confirm professional abilities",
      "to confirm foreign language skills"
    ],
    "answer": "to confirm the ability to study at a university"
  },
  {
    "question": "The university admission rate in Korea is ___ among OECD countries.",
    "options": [
      "average level",
      "lowest level",
      "highest level",
      "lower level"
    ],
    "answer": "highest level"
  },
  {
    "question": "Education in Korea is recognized as a method to ___ social status.",
    "options": [
      "lower",
      "raise",
      "unrelated to",
      "maintain"
    ],
    "answer": "raise"
  },
  {
    "question": "A gift given to people taking important exams in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "a meaning to give up on the exam",
      "a meaning to perform well on the exam",
      "a meaning to fail the exam",
      "a meaning of indifference towards the exam"
    ],
    "answer": "a meaning to perform well on the exam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traditionally, what is given as a gift to wish for success in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "yeot and chapssal-tteok",
      "fruits and chocolate",
      "flowers and cards",
      "books and pencils"
    ],
    "answer": "yeot and chapssal-tteok"
  },
  {
    "question": "When entering university, one that is not included in the special admissions category is ___.",
    "options": [
      "rural students",
      "overseas Koreans",
      "specialized high school graduates",
      "high-income students"
    ],
    "answer": "high-income students"
  },
  {
    "question": "The impact of Korea's high educational fervor on the Korean economy is ___.",
    "options": [
      "rapid economic development",
      "economic instability",
      "economic slowdown",
      "economic recession"
    ],
    "answer": "rapid economic development"
  },
  {
    "question": "The high educational zeal in Korea is mostly for the purpose of entering university ___",
    "options": [
      "entering university",
      "entering high school",
      "entering middle school",
      "entering elementary school"
    ],
    "answer": "entering university"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason parents spend a lot of money on private education during their children's middle and high school years is the children's ___.",
    "options": [
      "college entrance",
      "high school entrance",
      "middle school entrance",
      "elementary school entrance"
    ],
    "answer": "college entrance"
  },
  {
    "question": "The form of education that places a significant burden on parents is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "formal school education",
      "private education",
      "self-directed learning",
      "online learning"
    ],
    "answer": "private education"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, there is a phrase that expresses the difficult high school life, which is ___.",
    "options": [
      "3rd year syndrome, entrance exam hell",
      "1st year syndrome, entrance exam paradise",
      "2nd year syndrome, entrance exam hell",
      "3rd year syndrome, entrance exam paradise"
    ],
    "answer": "3rd year syndrome, entrance exam hell"
  },
  {
    "question": "The increase of 'Gireogi Appa' started in ___",
    "options": [
      "1980s",
      "Late 1990s",
      "Early 2000s",
      "2010s"
    ],
    "answer": "Late 1990s"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the characteristics of lifelong education are ___",
    "options": [
      "Conducted separately from school education",
      "Conducted alongside school education",
      "Replaces school education",
      "Supplemented by school education"
    ],
    "answer": "Conducted separately from school education"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the lifelong education center of the university operates ___.",
    "options": [
      "expert courses and certification courses",
      "elementary school courses",
      "middle school courses",
      "high school courses"
    ],
    "answer": "expert courses and certification courses"
  },
  {
    "question": "An example of lifelong education for the elderly recently conducted is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Smartphone education, SNS education",
      "English education, Chinese education",
      "Math education, Science education",
      "Music education, Art education"
    ],
    "answer": "Smartphone education, SNS education"
  },
  {
    "question": "The tuition for lifelong education programs is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "very expensive",
      "relatively expensive",
      "relatively cheap",
      "free"
    ],
    "answer": "relatively cheap"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason for the increase in lifelong education using the internet and other media is ___",
    "options": [
      "The cost of education is low",
      "It can be attended at a desired time",
      "The content of education is diverse",
      "There are many educational institutions"
    ],
    "answer": "It can be attended at a desired time"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not classified as an SNS in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "KakaoTalk",
      "Twitter",
      "Facebook",
      "Naver Webtoon"
    ],
    "answer": "Naver Webtoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most commonly used SNS in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "KakaoTalk",
      "Twitter",
      "Facebook",
      "Instagram"
    ],
    "answer": "KakaoTalk"
  },
  {
    "question": "A place where you cannot obtain information about finding a house in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "real estate agent",
      "neighbor",
      "internet",
      "coin karaoke room"
    ],
    "answer": "coin karaoke room"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is not an expense incurred in renting an apartment on a monthly basis is ___",
    "options": [
      "Deposit",
      "Monthly Rent",
      "Maintenance Fee",
      "Jeonse Deposit"
    ],
    "answer": "Jeonse Deposit"
  },
  {
    "question": "The security deposit for a jeonse is ___",
    "options": [
      "less than that for a jeonse and more than that for a monthly rent",
      "more than that for a jeonse and less than that for a monthly rent",
      "the sum of the deposits for jeonse and monthly rent",
      "the average of the deposits for jeonse and monthly rent"
    ],
    "answer": "less than that for a jeonse and more than that for a monthly rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among monthly rent and jeonse, ____ has a larger deposit.",
    "options": [
      "monthly rent",
      "jeonse",
      "both are the same",
      "it depends on the situation"
    ],
    "answer": "jeonse"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since the mid-2000s, the number of households living in ____ in Korea has increased.",
    "options": [
      "single-family home",
      "multi-family home",
      "townhouse",
      "apartment"
    ],
    "answer": "apartment"
  },
  {
    "question": "As the population concentrated in the city, ___ housing has gradually increased.",
    "options": [
      "single-family homes",
      "multi-family homes",
      "townhouses",
      "large-scale high-rise apartments"
    ],
    "answer": "large-scale high-rise apartments"
  },
  {
    "question": "The type of housing preferred by many Koreans today is ___.",
    "options": [
      "single-family home",
      "multi-family home",
      "townhouse",
      "apartment"
    ],
    "answer": "apartment"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason why ordinary people have difficulty finding a house in major cities in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "There is a shortage of houses",
      "House prices are high",
      "Rental prices are high",
      "There is a lack of housing policy"
    ],
    "answer": "House prices are high"
  },
  {
    "question": "The method used by the Korean government to address the housing issues of the common people is ___.",
    "options": [
      "establishing various housing policies",
      "reducing rent",
      "lowering house prices",
      "increasing housing supply"
    ],
    "answer": "establishing various housing policies"
  },
  {
    "question": "The housing policy implemented by the Korean government for economically disadvantaged people is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Construction of multi-family housing",
      "Rent reduction",
      "House price reduction",
      "Increase in housing quantity"
    ],
    "answer": "Construction of multi-family housing"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a housing policy of the Korean government.",
    "options": [
      "National Rental Housing",
      "Public Rental Housing",
      "Bogeumjari Housing",
      "Short-Term Auction Housing"
    ],
    "answer": "Short-Term Auction Housing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The primary target of the Korean government's housing supply policy is ___.",
    "options": [
      "multi-homeowners",
      "low-income individuals or the homeless",
      "high-income individuals",
      "foreigners"
    ],
    "answer": "low-income individuals or the homeless"
  },
  {
    "question": "The event that usually takes place on 'son-eun-nal' in Korea is ____.",
    "options": [
      "moving",
      "birthday party",
      "entrance ceremony",
      "graduation ceremony"
    ],
    "answer": "moving"
  },
  {
    "question": "When you have a lot of luggage and not much time, a convenient service to use in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "delivery service",
      "packing moving service",
      "chauffeur service",
      "delivery service"
    ],
    "answer": "packing moving service"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main residential types in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "owned, jeonse, monthly rent",
      "jeonse, monthly rent, half-jeonse",
      "owned, monthly rent, half-jeonse",
      "owned, jeonse, half-jeonse"
    ],
    "answer": "owned, jeonse, monthly rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year when South Korea completely overcame the foreign exchange crisis is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1999",
      "2000",
      "2001",
      "2002"
    ],
    "answer": "2001"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1960, the per capita national income of South Korea was ___.",
    "options": [
      "79 dollars",
      "800 dollars",
      "8,000 dollars",
      "80,000 dollars"
    ],
    "answer": "79 dollars"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year Korea experienced a foreign exchange crisis is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1995",
      "1996",
      "1997",
      "1998"
    ],
    "answer": "1997"
  },
  {
    "question": "The city that the Han River pass through in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "Busan",
      "Daegu",
      "Incheon",
      "Seoul"
    ],
    "answer": "Seoul"
  },
  {
    "question": "The industry that started to develop in Korea from the 1970s is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Agriculture",
      "Light industry",
      "Heavy and chemical industry",
      "Service industry"
    ],
    "answer": "Heavy and chemical industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The industrial structure of South Korea in the 2010s is primarily centered around ___ industries.",
    "options": [
      "agriculture and forestry",
      "manufacturing and service",
      "light industry and heavy chemical industry",
      "mining and energy"
    ],
    "answer": "manufacturing and service"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2014, Korea's per capita gross national income is ___",
    "options": [
      "$2,800",
      "$28,000",
      "$280,000",
      "$2,800,000"
    ],
    "answer": "$28,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "The dazzling economic growth of Korea is referred to as __________.",
    "options": [
      "Miracle on the Han River",
      "Miracle of Seoul",
      "Miracle of Economy",
      "Miracle of Industry"
    ],
    "answer": "Miracle on the Han River"
  },
  {
    "question": "The industry that South Korea developed in the 1960s is ___.",
    "options": [
      "heavy and chemical industry",
      "manufacturing",
      "light industry",
      "service industry"
    ],
    "answer": "light industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2013, Korea became the ___ largest trading country in the world.",
    "options": [
      "5th",
      "6th",
      "7th",
      "8th"
    ],
    "answer": "8th"
  },
  {
    "question": "The country that trades the most with Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "China, USA, Japan",
      "USA, Japan, UK",
      "China, USA, UK",
      "USA, Japan, France"
    ],
    "answer": "China, USA, Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2011, Korea's export amount was ___.",
    "options": [
      "10 billion dollars",
      "100 billion dollars",
      "500 billion dollars",
      "1 trillion dollars"
    ],
    "answer": "500 billion dollars"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year in which South Korea surpassed a trade volume of 1 trillion dollars is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1964",
      "1977",
      "1995",
      "2011"
    ],
    "answer": "2011"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2010s, the item with the highest proportion among Korea's top 10 trading items is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Semiconductors",
      "Petroleum products",
      "Automobiles",
      "Ships and marine structures"
    ],
    "answer": "Semiconductors"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first country that South Korea signed a free trade agreement (FTA) with is ___.",
    "options": [
      "United States",
      "India",
      "Chile",
      "EU"
    ],
    "answer": "Chile"
  },
  {
    "question": "The three major markets where South Korea reduces or eliminates tariffs when trading are ___.",
    "options": [
      "United States, China, EU",
      "United States, China, Japan",
      "United States, EU, Japan",
      "China, EU, Japan"
    ],
    "answer": "United States, China, EU"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year Korea joined the OECD is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "1994",
      "1996",
      "1998",
      "2000"
    ],
    "answer": "1996"
  },
  {
    "question": "The economic cooperation meeting held in Korea in 2005 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "ASEM",
      "APEC",
      "G20",
      "ASEAN"
    ],
    "answer": "APEC"
  },
  {
    "question": "The summit held in Seoul in 2010 was ___.",
    "options": [
      "ASEM",
      "APEC",
      "G20",
      "ASEAN"
    ],
    "answer": "G20"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year Korea was recognized as a member of OECD's DAC is ___.",
    "options": [
      "2007",
      "2008",
      "2009",
      "2010"
    ],
    "answer": "2009"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2015, the number of ASEAN countries that signed an FTA with Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "4 countries",
      "10 countries",
      "28 countries",
      "20 countries"
    ],
    "answer": "10 countries"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year when Korea was recognized as a member of the OECD Development Assistance Committee (DAC) is ___.",
    "options": [
      "2007",
      "2008",
      "2009",
      "2010"
    ],
    "answer": "2009"
  },
  {
    "question": "The characteristics of the countries that South Korea is actively helping are ___",
    "options": [
      "Countries with economic difficulties",
      "Militarily weak countries",
      "Countries with large populations",
      "Resource-rich countries"
    ],
    "answer": "Countries with economic difficulties"
  },
  {
    "question": "A person who is not satisfied with the interest rates offered by commercial banks can use ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "NongHyup",
      "Suhyup",
      "Post Office",
      "Mutual Savings Bank"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutual Savings Bank"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is needed to open a bank account in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "ID card",
      "passport",
      "foreign registration card",
      "driver's license"
    ],
    "answer": "ID card"
  },
  {
    "question": "The system that must be adhered to when conducting financial transactions in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Real-name Financial System",
      "Anonymous Financial System",
      "Real-name Financialization",
      "Anonymous Financialization"
    ],
    "answer": "Real-name Financial System"
  },
  {
    "question": "The documents required for a foreigner to open a bank account in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "Passport and Alien Registration Card",
      "ID and Passport",
      "Alien Registration Card and Driver's License",
      "Passport and Driver's License"
    ],
    "answer": "Passport and Alien Registration Card"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Typical savings products include ___.",
    "options": [
      "regular savings, time deposits, regular deposits",
      "time deposits, savings, stocks",
      "regular savings, savings, stocks",
      "time deposits, regular savings, stocks"
    ],
    "answer": "regular savings, time deposits, regular deposits"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the main characteristics of commercial banks and regional banks are generally ___.",
    "options": [
      "large and safe",
      "small and safe",
      "large and risky",
      "small and risky"
    ],
    "answer": "large and safe"
  },
  {
    "question": "The disadvantage of commercial banks and regional banks is that ___.",
    "options": [
      "The deposit interest rates are relatively low",
      "The deposit interest rates are relatively high",
      "The service is inconvenient",
      "There are few branches"
    ],
    "answer": "The deposit interest rates are relatively low"
  },
  {
    "question": "The characteristic of mutual savings banks is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "high interest rates",
      "large scale",
      "high safety",
      "many branches"
    ],
    "answer": "high interest rates"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main purpose of using a securities company is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "to invest in stocks or bonds",
      "to enroll in insurance",
      "to make a deposit",
      "to obtain a loan"
    ],
    "answer": "to invest in stocks or bonds"
  },
  {
    "question": "A market that opens once every three days in Korea is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "3-day market",
      "5-day market",
      "permanent market",
      "traditional market"
    ],
    "answer": "3-day market"
  },
  {
    "question": "The tax that needs to be paid when purchasing goods or eating food in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "income tax",
      "value-added tax",
      "local tax",
      "corporate tax"
    ],
    "answer": "value-added tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "When consumers purchase and use goods in Korea, what is stipulated by law as ___",
    "options": [
      "consumer rights",
      "consumer obligations",
      "product price",
      "product quality"
    ],
    "answer": "consumer rights"
  },
  {
    "question": "When a problem arises after purchasing a product and expert help is needed without a resolution, in Korea, you can receive help from ___.",
    "options": [
      "National Tax Service",
      "Korea Consumer Agency",
      "Cash Receipt Website",
      "Store where the product was purchased"
    ],
    "answer": "Korea Consumer Agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is a must-do when getting a job in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Write a work contract",
      "Submit a resume",
      "Prepare for an interview",
      "Submit proof photos"
    ],
    "answer": "Write a work contract"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is something that job seekers in Korea do not try to possess when looking for a job.",
    "options": [
      "Academic background",
      "Grades",
      "English score",
      "Hobbies"
    ],
    "answer": "Hobbies"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the situation of finding a job in Korea in the 2010s became ___",
    "options": [
      "less competitive",
      "more competitive",
      "unchanged",
      "weaker"
    ],
    "answer": "more competitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "To protect the rights of workers, it is essential to ___ when starting a job.",
    "options": [
      "negotiate wages",
      "draft an employment contract",
      "get free consultation",
      "access free medical services"
    ],
    "answer": "draft an employment contract"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not one of the three friends of winter (歲寒三友) in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Pine tree",
      "Bamboo",
      "Plum blossom",
      "Camellia"
    ],
    "answer": "Camellia"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traditional clothing worn only by women is ___",
    "options": [
      "Jam-bang-i",
      "Deung-geori",
      "Jang-ot",
      "Ma-go-ja"
    ],
    "answer": "Jang-ot"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not used in traditional rituals (祭禮).",
    "options": [
      "Gangsins (降神)",
      "Choheon (初獻)",
      "Chorae (醮禮)",
      "Dokchuk (讀祝)"
    ],
    "answer": "Chorae (醮禮)"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is inconsistent with the general principles of a ritual table for honoring ancestors.",
    "options": [
      "Ban Seo Gyeong Dong (飯西羹東)",
      "Eo Dong Yuk Seo (魚東肉西)",
      "Hong Dong Baek Seo (紅東白西)",
      "Seo Du Dong Mi (西頭東尾)"
    ],
    "answer": "Seo Du Dong Mi (西頭東尾)"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a blowing instrument (吹樂器) among traditional musical instruments in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Pipa",
      "Nabal",
      "Nagas",
      "Taepyeongso"
    ],
    "answer": "Pipa"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ does not use a mask.",
    "options": [
      "Swimming Dance",
      "Songpa Sandae Nori",
      "Goseong Ogwangdae Nori",
      "Kkokdugaksi Nori"
    ],
    "answer": "Kkokdugaksi Nori"
  },
  {
    "question": "The connection of ____ regarding the position of household gods in Korean folklore is correct.",
    "options": [
      "Eopsin - Well",
      "Jowangsin - Kitchen",
      "Seongjusin - Kimchi pot rack",
      "Teojusin - Granary"
    ],
    "answer": "Jowangsin - Kitchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "The character that does not appear in ‘Hahoe Byeolsin Gut Tal Nori’ is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Yangban",
      "Bune",
      "Cholangi",
      "Maltugi"
    ],
    "answer": "Maltugi"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ does not correspond to the 'Ten Symbols of Longevity' in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Crane",
      "Dragon",
      "Stream",
      "Bamboo"
    ],
    "answer": "Dragon"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not one of the five forbidden pungent vegetables in temples.",
    "options": [
      "leek",
      "chives",
      "garlic",
      "red pepper"
    ],
    "answer": "red pepper"
  },
  {
    "question": "The legend that is not the 'Gwangpo Legend' found in various regions across the country is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Baby Warrior Legend",
      "Jangjamot Legend",
      "Seolmundae Halman Legend",
      "Onui Himnaegi Legend"
    ],
    "answer": "Seolmundae Halman Legend"
  },
  {
    "question": "The instruments played in the military ceremony music (군례악) called 'Daechwita' are correctly listed as ___",
    "options": [
      "daegeum, dangpiri, haegeum, eoh",
      "daegeum, sorak, pyeonjeong, jeolgo",
      "taepyeongso, nabaal, janggu, jing",
      "taepyeongso, ajang, pyeonggyeong, chuk"
    ],
    "answer": "taepyeongso, nabaal, janggu, jing"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the correct order of the seasons is ___",
    "options": [
      "Usul - Gyeongchip - Baengno - Cheoseo",
      "Ipchun - Cheongmyeong - Mangjong - Gokwoo",
      "Baengno - Chuseok - Hanlo - Sanggang",
      "Cheongmyeong - Usul - Sohan - Dongji"
    ],
    "answer": "Baengno - Chuseok - Hanlo - Sanggang"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the correct connection of the five elements, five directions, and five colors of Yin-Yang and the Five Elements is ___",
    "options": [
      "Fire (火) - South (南) - White (白)",
      "Water (水) - North (北) - Black (黑)",
      "Wood (木) - West (西) - Blue (靑)",
      "Metal (金) - East (東) - Yellow (黃)"
    ],
    "answer": "Fire (火) - South (南) - White (白)"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not related to death in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Funeral",
      "Condolence",
      "Memorial",
      "Congratulatory"
    ],
    "answer": "Congratulatory"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mime performance (默劇) in which the characters' actions proceed without dialogue is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Bongsan Talchum",
      "Goseong Ogwangdae Nori",
      "Hahoe Byeolsin Gut Tal Nori",
      "Gangneung Gwanno Mask Drama"
    ],
    "answer": "Gangneung Gwanno Mask Drama"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the traditional Korean wedding ceremony, the procedure where the bride goes to the groom's home and first greets her in-laws is called ___",
    "options": [
      "marriage by arrangement",
      "exchanging gifts",
      "mating ceremony",
      "first greeting ceremony"
    ],
    "answer": "first greeting ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among the traditional Korean clothing, the garment that is composed of a separate upper and lower part and was primarily worn as formal clothing by officials is ___",
    "options": [
      "Cheollik",
      "Jangot",
      "Baeja",
      "Hwalot"
    ],
    "answer": "Cheollik"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a work by Danwon Kim Hong-do.",
    "options": [
      "<Chongseokjeong(叢石亭)>",
      "<Inwangjesaekdo(仁王霽色圖)>",
      "<Dodamsambong(島潭三峯)>",
      "<Seodang(書堂)>"
    ],
    "answer": "<Inwangjesaekdo(仁王霽色圖)>"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a traditional function of a shaman in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Divination",
      "Entertainment",
      "Healing",
      "Judiciary"
    ],
    "answer": "Judiciary"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a representative dish of Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Bulgogi",
      "Bibimbap",
      "Dongpo Pork",
      "Samgyetang"
    ],
    "answer": "Dongpo Pork"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traditional Korean dress worn by men when going out during the Joseon Dynasty is ___.",
    "options": [
      "chima",
      "jeogori",
      "durumagi",
      "jangot"
    ],
    "answer": "durumagi"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Joseon Dynasty, the traditional clothing worn by women in Korea when going out was ___",
    "options": [
      "skirt",
      "jeogori",
      "durumagi",
      "jangot"
    ],
    "answer": "jangot"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Joseon Dynasty, both men and women wear ___ on their feet when wearing hanbok.",
    "options": [
      "shoes",
      "socks",
      "beoseon",
      "dress shoes"
    ],
    "answer": "beoseon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the past, the kimchi made during kimjang in Korea was ___",
    "options": [
      "stored in the refrigerator",
      "buried in the ground",
      "stored in a box",
      "stored at room temperature"
    ],
    "answer": "buried in the ground"
  },
  {
    "question": "The staple food of Koreans is ___.",
    "options": [
      "rice",
      "bread",
      "noodles",
      "meat"
    ],
    "answer": "rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main components of a meal that Koreans typically eat in Korea are ____.",
    "options": [
      "rice, soup, side dishes",
      "bread, soup, salad",
      "noodles, broth, side dishes",
      "rice, soup, salad"
    ],
    "answer": "rice, soup, side dishes"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is primarily used as side dishes in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "vegetables or kimchi",
      "meat or fish",
      "bread or snacks",
      "fruit or vegetables"
    ],
    "answer": "vegetables or kimchi"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the representative fermented foods of Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Kimchi",
      "Ramen",
      "Tteokbokki",
      "Bibimbap"
    ],
    "answer": "Kimchi"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, we prepare kimjang ___",
    "options": [
      "before the cold winter",
      "before spring",
      "before summer",
      "before autumn"
    ],
    "answer": "before the cold winter"
  },
  {
    "question": "The food that Koreans have enjoyed eating since long ago is __.",
    "options": [
      "tteok",
      "fried chicken",
      "la galbi",
      "ramen"
    ],
    "answer": "tteok"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the food that must be present during weddings, memorial services, holidays, and birthdays is ___.",
    "options": [
      "rice cake",
      "kimchi",
      "soybean paste",
      "pork belly"
    ],
    "answer": "rice cake"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a traditional Korean food.",
    "options": [
      "Baeksukgi",
      "Injeolmi",
      "Yakgwa",
      "Jeolpyeon"
    ],
    "answer": "Yakgwa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Representative dishes of Korea are mainly ___.",
    "options": [
      "eaten with rice or enjoyed separately",
      "only eaten with rice",
      "enjoyed separately only",
      "eaten with side dishes"
    ],
    "answer": "eaten with rice or enjoyed separately"
  },
  {
    "question": "Harvesting is an action primarily done ___.",
    "options": [
      "in spring",
      "in summer",
      "in fall",
      "in winter"
    ],
    "answer": "in fall"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yangban refers to people from ___.",
    "options": [
      "Goguryeo Dynasty",
      "Baekje Dynasty",
      "Silla Dynasty",
      "Joseon Dynasty"
    ],
    "answer": "Joseon Dynasty"
  },
  {
    "question": "The function of ondol is to ___ the room.",
    "options": [
      "cool",
      "warm",
      "cook",
      "boil"
    ],
    "answer": "warm"
  },
  {
    "question": "The daecheongmaru is located ___ in a traditional Korean house.",
    "options": [
      "inside the room",
      "outside the room",
      "between rooms",
      "kitchen"
    ],
    "answer": "between rooms"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yangban refers to the ____ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "lower class",
      "middle class",
      "upper class",
      "all classes"
    ],
    "answer": "upper class"
  },
  {
    "question": "The representative cities where Hanok villages are located are ___.",
    "options": [
      "Busan, Daegu",
      "Jeonju, Seoul",
      "Gwangju, Daejeon",
      "Incheon, Ulsan"
    ],
    "answer": "Jeonju, Seoul"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hanok is a traditional house of ___.",
    "options": [
      "China",
      "Japan",
      "Korea",
      "Vietnam"
    ],
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hanok is divided based on the materials used for the roof ___",
    "options": [
      "by size",
      "by location",
      "by the materials used for the roof",
      "by construction year"
    ],
    "answer": "by the materials used for the roof"
  },
  {
    "question": "The material used for the roof of a thatched house is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "tiles",
      "iron",
      "rice straw",
      "wood"
    ],
    "answer": "rice straw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hanbok is a traditional clothing of ___",
    "options": [
      "China",
      "Japan",
      "Korea",
      "Vietnam"
    ],
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "The current hanbok has inherited its form from the ____ Dynasty.",
    "options": [
      "Goguryeo",
      "Baekje",
      "Silla",
      "Joseon"
    ],
    "answer": "Joseon"
  },
  {
    "question": "The material used to make Hanbok in winter is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Sambe",
      "Mosi",
      "Silk",
      "Cotton"
    ],
    "answer": "Silk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Currently, hanbok is mainly worn during ____.",
    "options": [
      "daily",
      "holidays",
      "work",
      "exercise"
    ],
    "answer": "holidays"
  },
  {
    "question": "The hanbok, which is consistently popular in Korea today, is ___",
    "options": [
      "holiday hanbok",
      "wedding hanbok",
      "everyday hanbok",
      "first birthday hanbok"
    ],
    "answer": "everyday hanbok"
  },
  {
    "question": "Considering that the pants and skirts of hanbok were designed to accommodate sitting in everyday life in Korea, ___",
    "options": [
      "living while standing",
      "walking",
      "running",
      "living while sitting"
    ],
    "answer": "living while sitting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since the 2010s, there has been an increasing phenomenon of ____ during Korean holidays.",
    "options": [
      "children going to their hometowns",
      "parents going to large cities",
      "parents going abroad",
      "children going abroad"
    ],
    "answer": "parents going to large cities"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the representative holidays of Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Christmas",
      "Chuseok",
      "Seollal",
      "Easter"
    ],
    "answer": "Seollal"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the ceremony that Koreans perform on the morning of Seollal is ___",
    "options": [
      "Charye",
      "Seongmyo",
      "Sebae",
      "Eating Tteokguk"
    ],
    "answer": "Charye"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the act of bowing deeply to the elders in the family is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "Charye",
      "Seongmyeo",
      "Sebae",
      "Tteokguk eating"
    ],
    "answer": "Sebae"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, On New Year's Day, what elders give to young children is ___.",
    "options": [
      "tteokguk",
      "seolbim",
      "sebaetdon",
      "yunnori"
    ],
    "answer": "sebaetdon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Dressing children in new clothes for Lunar New Year is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "Tteokguk",
      "Seolbim",
      "Sebae-don",
      "Yutnori"
    ],
    "answer": "Seolbim"
  },
  {
    "question": "The representative food of Seollal is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Kimchi stew",
      "Rice cake soup",
      "Bibimbap",
      "Pork belly"
    ],
    "answer": "Rice cake soup"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traditional game that Koreans traditionally enjoy during Seollal is ___",
    "options": [
      "Yutnori",
      "Soccer",
      "Badminton",
      "Table Tennis"
    ],
    "answer": "Yutnori"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, seongmyolan means ____.",
    "options": [
      "Visiting and caring for an ancestor's grave",
      "Preparing food to honor ancestors",
      "Storing the relics of ancestors",
      "Passing down stories of ancestors"
    ],
    "answer": "Visiting and caring for an ancestor's grave"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the reason for flying kites on the first full moon of the year is ___",
    "options": [
      "to send away bad luck",
      "to attract good fortune",
      "to convey wishes to the gods",
      "to make one's name known"
    ],
    "answer": "to send away bad luck"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Jeongwol Daeboreum is on the lunar ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "January 1st",
      "January 15th",
      "December 31st",
      "December 15th"
    ],
    "answer": "January 15th"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, On the morning of the first full moon of the year, I shout ___.",
    "options": [
      "Take my luck away",
      "Take my heat away",
      "Take my health away",
      "Take my happiness away"
    ],
    "answer": "Take my heat away"
  },
  {
    "question": "During Jeongwol Daeboreum, Koreans eat ____.",
    "options": [
      "five-grain rice and seasoned vegetables",
      "rice cake soup and kimchi",
      "bibimbap and soybean paste soup",
      "ginseng chicken soup and kimchi"
    ],
    "answer": "five-grain rice and seasoned vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the reason for adding pine needles when steaming songpyeon is ___",
    "options": [
      "to enhance the flavor of songpyeon",
      "to prevent songpyeon from sticking together",
      "to make songpyeon look more beautiful",
      "to make songpyeon firmer"
    ],
    "answer": "to prevent songpyeon from sticking together"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the ingredient found in pine needles ____.",
    "options": [
      "enhances the taste of Songpyeon",
      "prevents Songpyeon from spoiling easily",
      "makes the color of Songpyeon brighter",
      "makes the size of Songpyeon larger"
    ],
    "answer": "prevents Songpyeon from spoiling easily"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, During the holidays, many people go to their ___.",
    "options": [
      "overseas",
      "large cities",
      "hometowns",
      "mountain villages"
    ],
    "answer": "hometowns"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chuseok corresponds to the lunar ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "July 15",
      "August 15",
      "September 15",
      "October 15"
    ],
    "answer": "August 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Chuseok is ___",
    "options": [
      "the time to start farming",
      "the time for finishing farming and harvesting grains",
      "the time to prepare for farming",
      "the time to plan for farming"
    ],
    "answer": "the time for finishing farming and harvesting grains"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before Chuseok, people usually ___",
    "options": [
      "fireworks",
      "ritual ceremony",
      "weeding",
      "festival"
    ],
    "answer": "weeding"
  },
  {
    "question": "The representative food of Chuseok is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Kimchi",
      "Bibimbap",
      "Songpyeon",
      "Tteokguk"
    ],
    "answer": "Songpyeon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Songpyeon is usually made in the shape of ___.",
    "options": [
      "star shape",
      "moon shape",
      "sun shape",
      "flower shape"
    ],
    "answer": "moon shape"
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a legend that if you make songpyeon beautifully, good things will happen, and that good thing is ___.",
    "options": [
      "to give birth to a beautiful daughter",
      "to become rich",
      "to become healthy",
      "to receive good fortune"
    ],
    "answer": "to give birth to a beautiful daughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the time of the year when the moon is the biggest and brightest is ____.",
    "options": [
      "New Year's Day",
      "Lunar New Year",
      "Chuseok",
      "Christmas"
    ],
    "answer": "Chuseok"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traditional activity enjoyed during Chuseok night is ___.",
    "options": [
      "fireworks",
      "moon viewing or Ganggangsullae dance",
      "snowball fight",
      "tree climbing"
    ],
    "answer": "moon viewing or Ganggangsullae dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main ingredient used to make Songpyeon is ___.",
    "options": [
      "wheat flour",
      "rice",
      "potato",
      "buckwheat"
    ],
    "answer": "rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "On Chuseok night, we ___ while looking at the full moon.",
    "options": [
      "sing",
      "dance",
      "make a wish",
      "exercise"
    ],
    "answer": "make a wish"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2015, the religion with the highest percentage among Koreans is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Buddhism",
      "Protestantism",
      "Catholicism",
      "Confucianism"
    ],
    "answer": "Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to a 2015 survey by Korean Gallup, the proportion of Koreans aged 18 and older with ___ is at a certain percentage.",
    "options": [
      "30%",
      "40%",
      "50%",
      "60%"
    ],
    "answer": "50%"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the era when Confucianism was adopted as the ideology for national governance is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Three Kingdoms Period",
      "Neolithic Era",
      "Joseon Dynasty",
      "Japanese Occupation"
    ],
    "answer": "Joseon Dynasty"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Confucianism is often perceived more as ___ rather than a religion.",
    "options": [
      "a value system",
      "a culture",
      "a discipline",
      "an art"
    ],
    "answer": "a value system"
  },
  {
    "question": "Protestantism has been widely recognized in Korea through the ___.",
    "options": [
      "establishment of hospitals and schools",
      "participation in international events",
      "cultural activities",
      "sports activities"
    ],
    "answer": "establishment of hospitals and schools"
  },
  {
    "question": "The oldest religion for Koreans is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Buddhism",
      "Christianity",
      "Shamanism",
      "Catholicism"
    ],
    "answer": "Shamanism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason people used to visit shamans in the past is ____ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "to predict the future",
      "to prevent bad events",
      "to recover health",
      "to gain wealth"
    ],
    "answer": "to prevent bad events"
  },
  {
    "question": "When curious about the future, people in Korea ___",
    "options": [
      "consulted a shaman",
      "prayed to a shaman",
      "held a ritual for a shaman",
      "gave money to a shaman"
    ],
    "answer": "consulted a shaman"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shamans play a role in connecting gods and people ___",
    "options": [
      "connecting gods and people",
      "restoring people's health",
      "increasing people's wealth",
      "managing temples"
    ],
    "answer": "connecting gods and people"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, ____ is believed to have sacred energy.",
    "options": [
      "wood and stone",
      "water and fire",
      "soil and wind",
      "sky and earth"
    ],
    "answer": "wood and stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the sacred tree that protects the village is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Pine tree",
      "Crepe myrtle",
      "Dangsanja",
      "Ginkgo tree"
    ],
    "answer": "Dangsanja"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ in Korea is related to the act of fortune-telling before important events or weddings.",
    "options": [
      "Buddhism",
      "Christianity",
      "Shamanism",
      "Catholicism"
    ],
    "answer": "Shamanism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The role of a shaman is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "to communicate with gods",
      "to protect the village",
      "to assist with farming",
      "to comfort people"
    ],
    "answer": "to communicate with gods"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason why ancient Koreans believed that there were deities in the house was ___",
    "options": [
      "to protect the house",
      "to decorate the house",
      "to clean the house",
      "to make the house bigger"
    ],
    "answer": "to protect the house"
  },
  {
    "question": "The correct description of Samshin is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Samshin is a deity found in the kitchen.",
      "Samshin helps give birth to children.",
      "Samshin brings misfortune to the household.",
      "Samshin helps one become rich."
    ],
    "answer": "Samshin helps give birth to children."
  },
  {
    "question": "After performing rituals to the Three Gods, the behavior of people is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "bowing",
      "dancing",
      "singing",
      "sleeping"
    ],
    "answer": "bowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason why ancient people set up the samshin statue in the main room is ___",
    "options": [
      "to wish for the child's health",
      "to become wealthy",
      "to protect the house",
      "to have more children"
    ],
    "answer": "to wish for the child's health"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, ____ is not a suitable example of a foreign religion.",
    "options": [
      "Myeongdong Cathedral",
      "Jeongdong Church",
      "Islamic Mosque",
      "Jogyesa Temple"
    ],
    "answer": "Jogyesa Temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korea recognizes freedom of ___",
    "options": [
      "Buddhism",
      "Christianity",
      "all religions",
      "Confucianism"
    ],
    "answer": "all religions"
  },
  {
    "question": "The foreign religion that spread to Korea the earliest is ___",
    "options": [
      "Buddhism",
      "Christianity",
      "Confucianism",
      "Islam"
    ],
    "answer": "Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The era when Confucianism began to take root in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Three Kingdoms Period",
      "Goguryeo",
      "Baekje",
      "Late Goryeo"
    ],
    "answer": "Late Goryeo"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the Confucian teachings that are naturally followed in daily life are ___.",
    "options": [
      "respect for elders",
      "intimate relationships",
      "material abundance",
      "personal freedom"
    ],
    "answer": "respect for elders"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main reason for visiting a temple in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "Tourism or experience",
      "Religious faith",
      "Academic research",
      "Social obligation"
    ],
    "answer": "Tourism or experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "If it is not designated as an important cultural property in Korea, it is ___",
    "options": [
      "traditional food",
      "Buddha statue in a temple",
      "pagoda in a temple",
      "old cathedral"
    ],
    "answer": "traditional food"
  },
  {
    "question": "Catholicism came to Korea in ___.",
    "options": [
      "16th century",
      "17th century",
      "18th century",
      "19th century"
    ],
    "answer": "17th century"
  },
  {
    "question": "Protestantism is known to have entered Korea in the ___ century.",
    "options": [
      "16th century",
      "17th century",
      "18th century",
      "19th century"
    ],
    "answer": "19th century"
  },
  {
    "question": "The indigenous religion created in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Catholicism and Protestantism",
      "Islam and Cheondoism",
      "Won Buddhism and Cheondoism",
      "Catholicism and Islam"
    ],
    "answer": "Won Buddhism and Cheondoism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The religion that was banned or oppressed during the Joseon Dynasty is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Catholicism",
      "Protestantism",
      "Islam",
      "Won Buddhism"
    ],
    "answer": "Catholicism"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, the letter inviting to a wedding is ___.",
    "options": [
      "wedding invitation",
      "congratulatory money",
      "traditional ceremony",
      "the main mourner"
    ],
    "answer": "wedding invitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, The purpose of an invitation card is ___.",
    "options": [
      "a letter inviting to a wedding",
      "a letter inviting to a birthday party",
      "a letter inviting to a company gathering",
      "a letter inviting to a funeral"
    ],
    "answer": "a letter inviting to a wedding"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, Congratulations money is mainly given to express  ___",
    "options": [
      "condolences",
      "congratulations",
      "gratitude",
      "apology"
    ],
    "answer": "congratulations"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, The condolence money is given ___ to the family experiencing a loss.",
    "options": [
      "at a wedding",
      "at a birthday party",
      "at a company meeting",
      "to the family experiencing a loss"
    ],
    "answer": "to the family experiencing a loss"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, In the ritual ceremony, the family performs the action of bowing to the ancestors ___.",
    "options": [
      "twice",
      "three times",
      "once",
      "four times"
    ],
    "answer": "twice"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, The item used for a cash gift is ___.",
    "options": [
      "candle holder",
      "flower basket",
      "fruit basket",
      "gift box"
    ],
    "answer": "candle holder"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, The appearance of the ritual table varies according to ___",
    "options": [
      "age",
      "gender",
      "religion",
      "region"
    ],
    "answer": "religion"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, The traditional greeting to both families after the wedding ceremony is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Pyeo-baek",
      "Sang-ju",
      "Sang-mo",
      "Sang-ga"
    ],
    "answer": "Pyeo-baek"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, The color of the clothes worn by visitors who come to comfort the bereaved at a funeral is ___.",
    "options": [
      "white",
      "black",
      "blue",
      "red"
    ],
    "answer": "black"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, The items for the doljabi have ___",
    "options": [
      "meanings based on colors",
      "meanings based on shapes",
      "meanings for each item",
      "meanings based on size"
    ],
    "answer": "meanings for each item"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, ____ is primarily given as a gift for a first birthday party.",
    "options": [
      "toys",
      "clothes",
      "gold rings",
      "books"
    ],
    "answer": "gold rings"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the meaning of gifting a gold ring is ____.",
    "options": [
      "to wish for the baby's health",
      "to wish for the baby's luck",
      "to wish that the baby grows up in a valuable and pure way",
      "to wish for the baby's future success"
    ],
    "answer": "to wish that the baby grows up in a valuable and pure way"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the doljabi, when a baby grabs the thread, it symbolizes ____.",
    "options": [
      "wealth",
      "longevity",
      "wisdom",
      "health"
    ],
    "answer": "longevity"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, what is generally eaten on birthdays is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Kimchi stew",
      "Soybean paste stew",
      "Seaweed soup",
      "Soft tofu stew"
    ],
    "answer": "Seaweed soup"
  },
  {
    "question": "The birthdays that hold special significance in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "the first birthday and the 60th birthday",
      "the first birthday and the 50th birthday",
      "the first birthday and the 40th birthday",
      "the first birthday and the 30th birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "the first birthday and the 60th birthday"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, a celebration is held after ___ days have passed since a baby is born.",
    "options": [
      "50 days",
      "100 days",
      "150 days",
      "200 days"
    ],
    "answer": "100 days"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the baby's first birthday is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "Baekil Janchi",
      "Doljanchi",
      "Hwangap Janchi",
      "Chilsun Janchi"
    ],
    "answer": "Doljanchi"
  },
  {
    "question": "The 60th birthday in Korea is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "Baekil party",
      "Doljanchi",
      "Hwangap party",
      "Chilsun party"
    ],
    "answer": "Hwangap party"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the past, in Korea, living to the age of sixty was considered ___",
    "options": [
      "a great blessing.",
      "a common occurrence.",
      "an unfortunate thing.",
      "not a big deal."
    ],
    "answer": "a great blessing."
  },
  {
    "question": "These days, the celebration that is regarded as more significant than a Hwangap party in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "100-day celebration",
      "1st birthday party",
      "Hwangap party",
      "70th birthday party"
    ],
    "answer": "70th birthday party"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the first birthday celebration, ___ takes place.",
    "options": [
      "a doljabi ceremony",
      "a dance event",
      "a singing event",
      "a gift-giving event"
    ],
    "answer": "a doljabi ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2000s in Korea, when moving houses, people would ___ to their neighbors.",
    "options": [
      "give rice cakes",
      "give money",
      "give gifts",
      "ask for the neighbor's home phone number"
    ],
    "answer": "give rice cakes"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is organized in Korea to maintain connections even after graduation.",
    "options": [
      "Alumni Association",
      "Regional Association",
      "Hometown Association",
      "Classmate Association"
    ],
    "answer": "Classmate Association"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korean, In social life, people tend to help and rely on each other in ___.",
    "options": [
      "Elementary School",
      "Middle School",
      "High School or University",
      "Graduate School"
    ],
    "answer": "High School or University"
  },
  {
    "question": "The value that is considered important when dealing with parents in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "filial piety",
      "patience",
      "love",
      "independence"
    ],
    "answer": "filial piety"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Visiting parents during holidays or on their birthdays is a behavior that stems from the traditional value of ___.",
    "options": [
      "Filial piety",
      "Etiquette",
      "Holidays",
      "Ritual"
    ],
    "answer": "Filial piety"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korea is a country that emphasizes ___.",
    "options": [
      "filial piety",
      "etiquette",
      "traditional holidays",
      "rituals"
    ],
    "answer": "etiquette"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, An example of etiquette is ___.",
    "options": [
      "honorifics",
      "holidays",
      "rituals",
      "meals"
    ],
    "answer": "honorifics"
  },
  {
    "question": "The gesture used to greet someone with a sense of respect in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "bowing",
      "waving",
      "closing one's eyes",
      "clapping"
    ],
    "answer": "bowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, you bow to parents, elders, or bereaved family members during ___",
    "options": [
      "Birthday",
      "Holidays, Weddings, Funerals",
      "Christmas",
      "New Year"
    ],
    "answer": "Holidays, Weddings, Funerals"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The proverb \"A close neighbor is better than a distant cousin\" means ___",
    "options": [
      "A close neighbor is more valuable",
      "A distant relative is more valuable",
      "Relatives are more important than neighbors",
      "Neighbors are more important than relatives"
    ],
    "answer": "A close neighbor is more valuable"
  },
  {
    "question": "The term \"neighboring cousin\" means ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "close neighbor",
      "distant neighbor",
      "neighborhood friend",
      "relative living nearby"
    ],
    "answer": "close neighbor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Korean people consider important is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Connection",
      "Blood relation",
      "Regional ties",
      "Friendship"
    ],
    "answer": "Connection"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is considered important in a Korean family.",
    "options": [
      "family tree",
      "report card",
      "resume",
      "self-introduction"
    ],
    "answer": "family tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "The name of the organization that people create in a newly settled place is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Alumni Association",
      "Regional Association",
      "Hometown Association",
      "Social Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Hometown Association"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is valued for forming academic connections in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Elementary school",
      "Middle school",
      "High school and university",
      "Graduate school"
    ],
    "answer": "High school and university"
  },
  {
    "question": "The gates that were built around the capital city of Hanyang during the Joseon Dynasty are commonly referred to as the Four Great Gates (사대문). ____ is the correct name and direction of the gates.",
    "options": [
      "Heunginjimun, Sukjeongmun, Sungnyeemun, Dongnimmun",
      "Sungnyeemun, Sukjeongmun, Heunginjimun, Dongnimmun",
      "Heunginjimun, Dongnimmun, Sungnyeemun, Sukjeongmun",
      "Sungnyeemun, Heunginjimun, Dongnimmun, Sukjeongmun"
    ],
    "answer": "Heunginjimun, Dongnimmun, Sungnyeemun, Sukjeongmun"
  },
  {
    "question": "The correct connection between ancient Korean states and shamanistic rituals is ___",
    "options": [
      "Dongye - Yeonggo",
      "Buyeo - Mucheong",
      "Baekje - Sodog",
      "Goguryeo - Dongmaeng"
    ],
    "answer": "Goguryeo - Dongmaeng"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not included in the four major holidays of the Joseon Dynasty.",
    "options": [
      "Dano",
      "Chilseok",
      "Hansik",
      "Chuseok"
    ],
    "answer": "Chilseok"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not an educational institution established in the early modern period in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Sabuhakdang",
      "Yukyeonggongwon",
      "Wonsan Haksa",
      "Baejaehakdang"
    ],
    "answer": "Sabuhakdang"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Among the existing ancient songs, the one that is strongly magical and sung collectively is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gongmudohaga (公無渡河歌)",
      "Hwangjoga (黃鳥歌)",
      "Gujiga (龜旨歌)",
      "Jeong-eupsa (井邑詞)"
    ],
    "answer": "Gujiga (龜旨歌)"
  },
  {
    "question": "The oldest existing Korean cookbook written by Lady Jang of Andong is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gyuhap Chongseo",
      "Sangayo Log",
      "Suwon Japbang",
      "Eumsik Dimibang"
    ],
    "answer": "Eumsik Dimibang"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a UNESCO World Document Heritage.",
    "options": [
      "Donguibogam",
      "The Declaration of Independence of Korea",
      "Saemaul Undong records",
      "May 18 Democratic Uprising records"
    ],
    "answer": "The Declaration of Independence of Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "The altar made by Emperor Gojong of the Korean Empire to conduct the Rite of Jecheong is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Hwanggudan",
      "Chamseongdan",
      "Cheonjeondan",
      "Sajikdan"
    ],
    "answer": "Hwanggudan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The title of the book that was the first modern Korean literary work designated as a registered cultural heritage by the Cultural Heritage Administration is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Mujeong",
      "Jindallae Flower",
      "Silence of the Lover",
      "Orangya Flower"
    ],
    "answer": "Jindallae Flower"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a building that constitutes a Seowon (書院) from the Joseon Dynasty ___",
    "options": [
      "Sadang (祠堂)",
      "Gangdang (講堂)",
      "Dongjae (東齋), Seojae (西齋)",
      "Gyubang (閨房)"
    ],
    "answer": "Gyubang (閨房)"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, ____ is not a UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage.",
    "options": [
      "Jikji Simche Yojeol",
      "Jongmyo Jerye and Ritual Music",
      "Tug-of-war",
      "Nongak"
    ],
    "answer": "Jikji Simche Yojeol"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first officially designated Confucian academy of the Joseon Dynasty is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Namgye Seowon",
      "Dodong Seowon",
      "Sosu Seowon",
      "Oksan Seowon"
    ],
    "answer": "Sosu Seowon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The oldest woodblock print is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Tripitaka Koreana",
      "Goryeo Tripitaka",
      "Jikji Simche Yojeol",
      "Mugujonggwang Daedaranigyeong"
    ],
    "answer": "Mugujonggwang Daedaranigyeong"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ of the central governing bodies of the Joseon Dynasty corresponds to '3sa'.",
    "options": [
      "Seonggyungwan",
      "Hongmungwan",
      "Uigeumbu",
      "Hansungbu"
    ],
    "answer": "Hongmungwan"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is not a hyangga from the Silla period.",
    "options": [
      "Hyesungga",
      "Cheongsanbyeolgok",
      "Ujeokga",
      "Changiparangga"
    ],
    "answer": "Cheongsanbyeolgok"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ was introduced during the Goryeo Dynasty.",
    "options": [
      "red pepper",
      "sweet potato",
      "pepper",
      "peanut"
    ],
    "answer": "pepper"
  },
  {
    "question": "The record of royal weddings in the Joseon Dynasty is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Taesil Uigwe (胎室儀軌)",
      "Garye Dogam Uigwe (嘉禮都監儀軌)",
      "Boinso Uigwe (寶印所儀軌)",
      "Daesarye Uigwe (大射禮儀軌)"
    ],
    "answer": "Garye Dogam Uigwe (嘉禮都監儀軌)"
  },
  {
    "question": "A correct explanation about the government offices during the Joseon Dynasty is _____",
    "options": [
      "Saganwon - drafted royal edicts.",
      "Hanseongbu - compiled city chronicles.",
      "Chungryeogwon - prepared diplomatic documents.",
      "Seungjeongwon - issued the king's commands."
    ],
    "answer": "Seungjeongwon - issued the king's commands."
  },
  {
    "question": "The month in which the protests by citizens advocating for a direct presidential election amendment spread in 1987 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "May",
      "June",
      "July",
      "August"
    ],
    "answer": "June"
  },
  {
    "question": "The period that influenced the democratization process of Korea is ___ after the period.",
    "options": [
      "1970s",
      "1980s",
      "1990s",
      "2000s"
    ],
    "answer": "1980s"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korea fundamentally adopts ___ form of democracy.",
    "options": [
      "direct democracy",
      "indirect democracy",
      "liberal democracy",
      "social democracy"
    ],
    "answer": "indirect democracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Korea has adopted a ___ system.",
    "options": [
      "presidential system",
      "parliamentary cabinet system",
      "monarchy",
      "republic"
    ],
    "answer": "presidential system"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first president of Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Yoon Bo-seon",
      "Park Chung-hee",
      "Syngman Rhee",
      "Roh Tae-woo"
    ],
    "answer": "Syngman Rhee"
  },
  {
    "question": "The 10th president of South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Choi Kyu-ha",
      "Chun Doo-hwan",
      "Roh Tae-woo",
      "Kim Young-sam"
    ],
    "answer": "Choi Kyu-ha"
  },
  {
    "question": "The 18th president of Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Roh Moo-hyun",
      "Lee Myung-bak",
      "Park Geun-hye",
      "Moon Jae-in"
    ],
    "answer": "Park Geun-hye"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the person who exercises the rights of a master is ___.",
    "options": [
      "President",
      "Member of Parliament",
      "Citizens",
      "Government"
    ],
    "answer": "Citizens"
  },
  {
    "question": "Park Chung-hee was the ____ president in South Korea?",
    "options": [
      "4th",
      "5th-9th",
      "10th",
      "11th-12th"
    ],
    "answer": "5th-9th"
  },
  {
    "question": "The date the Constitution of the Republic of Korea was established is ___.",
    "options": [
      "May 10, 1948",
      "July 17, 1948",
      "August 15, 1948",
      "August 15, 1945"
    ],
    "answer": "July 17, 1948"
  },
  {
    "question": "What the citizens of Gwangju demanded during the May 18th Democratic Movement was ___.",
    "options": [
      "cessation of military political intervention",
      "economic reform",
      "educational reform",
      "social reform"
    ],
    "answer": "cessation of military political intervention"
  },
  {
    "question": "What greatly influenced the democratization process in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Korea's economic development",
      "Korea's educational development",
      "May 18 Democracy Movement",
      "Freedom of expression in cyberspace"
    ],
    "answer": "May 18 Democracy Movement"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is well known that ___ president resigned from the presidency as a result of the 4.19 Revolution, among Lee Seung-man, Park Chung-hee, Roh Tae-woo, and Kim Young-sam.",
    "options": [
      "Lee Seung-man",
      "Park Chung-hee",
      "Roh Tae-woo",
      "Kim Young-sam"
    ],
    "answer": "Lee Seung-man"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main demand of the civic protests that spread nationwide in 1987 is ___.",
    "options": [
      "direct presidential elections",
      "the National Assembly's right to oversee government operations",
      "reduction of executive power",
      "increase in the power of the National Assembly"
    ],
    "answer": "direct presidential elections"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, basic local governments are classified as ___.",
    "options": [
      "Special Cities and Metropolitan Cities",
      "Cities, Counties, and Districts",
      "Provinces and Cities",
      "Special Cities and Provinces"
    ],
    "answer": "Cities, Counties, and Districts"
  },
  {
    "question": "The age at which voting rights are granted in Korea is ___ years old.",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2016, there is ___ special city in Korea's metropolitan municipalities.",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, early voting generally starts ___ before the election day.",
    "options": [
      "2 days",
      "3 days",
      "4 days",
      "5 days"
    ],
    "answer": "5 days"
  },
  {
    "question": "___ is necessary for early voting in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "ID card",
      "ballot",
      "early voting application",
      "resident registration card"
    ],
    "answer": "ID card"
  },
  {
    "question": "The national power of Korea is divided into ___.",
    "options": [
      "Executive, Legislative, Judicial",
      "Executive, Legislative, Police",
      "Executive, Judicial, Police",
      "Executive, Legislative, Defense"
    ],
    "answer": "Executive, Legislative, Judicial"
  },
  {
    "question": "The highest responsible person in the executive branch of South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Member of Parliament",
      "Prime Minister",
      "President",
      "Minister of Justice"
    ],
    "answer": "President"
  },
  {
    "question": "The term of the President of Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "4 years",
      "5 years",
      "6 years",
      "7 years"
    ],
    "answer": "5 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "The meaning of Cheongwadae is ___",
    "options": [
      "a house with a white roof",
      "a house with a blue roof",
      "a house with a red roof",
      "a house with a black roof"
    ],
    "answer": "a house with a blue roof"
  },
  {
    "question": "The department responsible for making laws in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "Executive Branch",
      "Legislative Branch",
      "Judicial Branch",
      "Police Department"
    ],
    "answer": "Legislative Branch"
  },
  {
    "question": "The institution responsible for the legislative role in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "State Council",
      "Prime Minister",
      "National Assembly",
      "Supreme Court"
    ],
    "answer": "National Assembly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The term of a National Assembly member of South Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "2 years",
      "3 years",
      "4 years",
      "5 years"
    ],
    "answer": "4 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the executive branch should prioritize ____ when handling affairs inside and outside the country.",
    "options": [
      "the will of the people",
      "established laws",
      "the constitution",
      "the president's instructions"
    ],
    "answer": "established laws"
  },
  {
    "question": "The institution that interprets and applies the law to resolve disputes in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "National Assembly",
      "Executive Branch",
      "Court",
      "Constitutional Court"
    ],
    "answer": "Court"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Constitutional Court of the Republic of Korea has ___ constitutional justices.",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ways to become a representative in Korea are ___.",
    "options": [
      "through gatherings and demonstrations",
      "through the media",
      "by running in various elections",
      "through the internet"
    ],
    "answer": "by running in various elections"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The main purpose of a gathering or demonstration is ___.",
    "options": [
      "to inform others of one's opinions or claims",
      "to become a representative",
      "to utilize the internet",
      "to express opinions through the media"
    ],
    "answer": "to inform others of one's opinions or claims"
  },
  {
    "question": "As democracy took root, people in Korea start to actively express ___",
    "options": [
      "interests and claims",
      "gender and age",
      "occupation and education",
      "nationality and religion"
    ],
    "answer": "interests and claims"
  },
  {
    "question": "The service initiated by the Korean government to resolve disputes over floor noise is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Floor Noise Mediation Service",
      "Floor Noise Reduction Service",
      "Floor Noise Elimination Service",
      "Floor Noise Adjustment Service"
    ],
    "answer": "Floor Noise Mediation Service"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is ___ that Japan caused a historical event in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "occupation of Korea as a colony",
      "war with Korea",
      "economic support for Korea",
      "cultural influence on Korea"
    ],
    "answer": "occupation of Korea as a colony"
  },
  {
    "question": "The United States has had a significant influence on South Korea since ____.",
    "options": [
      "World War I",
      "World War II",
      "Korean War",
      "Vietnam War"
    ],
    "answer": "World War II"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Korean War, Russia supported ___.",
    "options": [
      "North Korea",
      "China",
      "the United States",
      "South Korea"
    ],
    "answer": "North Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "The date when Korea escaped Japanese rule and welcomed liberation is ___.",
    "options": [
      "July 15, 1945",
      "August 15, 1945",
      "September 15, 1945",
      "October 15, 1945"
    ],
    "answer": "August 15, 1945"
  },
  {
    "question": "The years in which the Republic of Korea and the Democratic People's Republic of Korea were each established are ___.",
    "options": [
      "1945",
      "1946",
      "1947",
      "1948"
    ],
    "answer": "1948"
  },
  {
    "question": "The date when the Korean War started is ___.",
    "options": [
      "May 25, 1950",
      "June 25, 1950",
      "July 25, 1950",
      "August 25, 1950"
    ],
    "answer": "June 25, 1950"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year the Korean War ended was ___.",
    "options": [
      "1951",
      "1952",
      "1953",
      "1954"
    ],
    "answer": "1953"
  },
  {
    "question": "The year of the first inter-Korean summit meeting is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1998",
      "1999",
      "2000",
      "2001"
    ],
    "answer": "2000"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ has increased since the improvement of inter-Korean relations.",
    "options": [
      "Economic and cultural exchanges",
      "Military cooperation",
      "Political alliances",
      "Scientific and technological exchanges"
    ],
    "answer": "Economic and cultural exchanges"
  },
  {
    "question": "The location where the inter-Korean summit was held is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Seoul",
      "Pyongyang",
      "Panmunjom",
      "Kaesong"
    ],
    "answer": "Pyongyang"
  },
  {
    "question": "The names of the two leaders who met at the inter-Korean summit held in 2000 are ___.",
    "options": [
      "Kim Dae-jung, Kim Il-sung",
      "Kim Dae-jung, Kim Jong-il",
      "Roh Moo-hyun, Kim Jong-il",
      "Moon Jae-in, Kim Jong-un"
    ],
    "answer": "Kim Dae-jung, Kim Jong-il"
  },
  {
    "question": "What many Korean citizens and people around the world hope for is ___",
    "options": [
      "peaceful unification of the Korean Peninsula",
      "the Cold War between North and South",
      "threat of nuclear weapons from North Korea",
      "military integration between North and South"
    ],
    "answer": "peaceful unification of the Korean Peninsula"
  },
  {
    "question": "The four great powers surrounding the Korean Peninsula include China, Japan, the United States, and ___.",
    "options": [
      "Russia",
      "North Korea",
      "South Korea",
      "India"
    ],
    "answer": "Russia"
  },
  {
    "question": "The United States supported ____ during the Korean War.",
    "options": [
      "North Korea",
      "China",
      "Russia",
      "South Korea"
    ],
    "answer": "South Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dokdo is located in ___ of Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Seoul Special City",
      "Jeju Special Self-Governing Province",
      "Gyeongsangbuk-do Ulleung-gun",
      "Busan Metropolitan City"
    ],
    "answer": "Gyeongsangbuk-do Ulleung-gun"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sea around Dokdo is rich in ___.",
    "options": [
      "oil",
      "gold",
      "marine resources",
      "iron"
    ],
    "answer": "marine resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "Japan's attempt to list Dokdo as its territory in textbooks is ___ in Korea internationally",
    "options": [
      "being accepted",
      "not being accepted",
      "being received neutrally",
      "being ignored"
    ],
    "answer": "not being accepted"
  },
  {
    "question": "Documents proving that Dokdo has been Korean territory have existed since the ___ era.",
    "options": [
      "Goguryeo",
      "Baekje",
      "Silla Jijeungwang",
      "Joseon"
    ],
    "answer": "Silla Jijeungwang"
  },
  {
    "question": "The organization that stays on Dokdo and fulfills the mission of protecting Dokdo is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Coast Guard",
      "Navy",
      "Dokdo Security Unit",
      "Marine Police Agency"
    ],
    "answer": "Dokdo Security Unit"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the sports that commonly achieve good results in international competitions are ___.",
    "options": [
      "archery, taekwondo, short track, speed skating",
      "baseball, soccer",
      "basketball, archery",
      "short track, skiing"
    ],
    "answer": "archery, taekwondo, short track, speed skating"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, a popular sport that is widely enjoyed domestically is ___.",
    "options": [
      "baseball, soccer",
      "taekwondo",
      "short track, speed skating",
      "archery, shooting"
    ],
    "answer": "baseball, soccer"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the popular music genres primarily enjoyed include ___",
    "options": [
      "Gagok, Trot, Ballad, R&B",
      "Classical, Jazz, Blues, Rock",
      "Folk, Carol, Opera, Symphony",
      "Opera, Reggae, Punk, Metal"
    ],
    "answer": "Gagok, Trot, Ballad, R&B"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, A drama that receives nationwide attention is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "hit drama",
      "blockbuster drama",
      "national drama",
      "mega hit drama"
    ],
    "answer": "national drama"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the culture that is enjoyed and consumed by the majority of people is known as ___.",
    "options": [
      "Traditional culture",
      "Popular culture",
      "Native culture",
      "Modern culture"
    ],
    "answer": "Popular culture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hip-hop or dance music is mainly enjoyed by ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "children",
      "teenagers and young adults",
      "middle-aged and older adults",
      "elderly"
    ],
    "answer": "teenagers and young adults"
  },
  {
    "question": "The music genre primarily liked by the middle-aged and older generations in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "trot or ballad-style songs",
      "hip-hop or dance music",
      "classical or jazz music",
      "rock or metal music"
    ],
    "answer": "trot or ballad-style songs"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most enjoyed sport by people in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "swimming competition",
      "professional baseball game",
      "archery competition",
      "taekwondo competition"
    ],
    "answer": "professional baseball game"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sport that competes for popularity with professional baseball in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Archery",
      "Taekwondo",
      "Soccer",
      "Badminton"
    ],
    "answer": "Soccer"
  },
  {
    "question": "K-pop refers to ___",
    "options": [
      "traditional Korean music",
      "Korean popular music",
      "Korean classical music",
      "Korean opera"
    ],
    "answer": "Korean popular music"
  },
  {
    "question": "The music genre that K-pop mainly refers to is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "dance music, hip-hop",
      "classical, jazz",
      "rock, metal",
      "country, blues"
    ],
    "answer": "dance music, hip-hop"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since the late 1990s, the Korean pop culture that spread mainly in Asia is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Hallyu",
      "K-pop",
      "Hanbok",
      "Hansik"
    ],
    "answer": "Hallyu"
  },
  {
    "question": "The start of the Korean Wave (한류) is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1980s",
      "late 1990s",
      "early 2000s",
      "early 2010s"
    ],
    "answer": "late 1990s"
  },
  {
    "question": "The period when K-pop began to seriously expand overseas is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1990s",
      "2000s",
      "2010s",
      "2020s"
    ],
    "answer": "2000s"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Korean drama that initially popularized the Korean Wave and gained great popularity in countries like Japan, China, and Southeast Asia is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Winter Sonata",
      "Descendants of the Sun",
      "Goblin",
      "Crash Landing on You"
    ],
    "answer": "Winter Sonata"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among foreigners, those who can stay in Korea without a time limit are ___",
    "options": [
      "Those who have applied for permanent residency",
      "Those who love Korea",
      "Those who have invested in Korea",
      "Those who are fluent in Korean"
    ],
    "answer": "Those who have applied for permanent residency"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, a VISA is generally called '___'.",
    "options": [
      "passport",
      "sajeung",
      "residence permit",
      "entry permit"
    ],
    "answer": "sajeung"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Islamic village in Seoul is located in ___.",
    "options": [
      "Guro-gu Garibong-dong",
      "Yongsan-gu Itaewon-dong",
      "Seocho-gu Bangbae-dong",
      "Dongdaemun-gu Gwanghui-dong"
    ],
    "answer": "Yongsan-gu Itaewon-dong"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ansan, Gyeonggi-do, there is a ___.",
    "options": [
      "Borderless Village",
      "Chinatown",
      "Japan Town",
      "Mongolian Village"
    ],
    "answer": "Borderless Village"
  },
  {
    "question": "The place where Ms. Marie Helene opened a free clinic in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Gangnam-gu, Seoul",
      "Jongno-gu, Seoul",
      "Siheung-dong, Seoul",
      "Dongdaemun-gu, Seoul"
    ],
    "answer": "Siheung-dong, Seoul"
  },
  {
    "question": "The name of the school founded by Dr. Eom Neul-ri is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Hanminjok School",
      "Korean Language School",
      "Korean Culture School",
      "Korean History School"
    ],
    "answer": "Hanminjok School"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, a trial for an incident can be held up to ___ times.",
    "options": [
      "1st",
      "2nd",
      "3rd",
      "4th"
    ],
    "answer": "3rd"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first trial in Korea is conducted in ___.",
    "options": [
      "Supreme Court",
      "High Court",
      "District Court",
      "Constitutional Court"
    ],
    "answer": "District Court"
  },
  {
    "question": "The institution that enforces the law in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Police and Prosecutors",
      "National Assembly",
      "Government",
      "Constitutional Court"
    ],
    "answer": "Police and Prosecutors"
  },
  {
    "question": "The phone number to report and receive assistance from the police is ___.",
    "options": [
      "119",
      "112",
      "114",
      "120"
    ],
    "answer": "112"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the investigation results from the law enforcement agency determine that there are violations of the law by the suspect, in Korea ___.",
    "options": [
      "punish the criminal directly",
      "apply to the court to punish the criminal",
      "hand over the criminal to the police",
      "deport the criminal overseas"
    ],
    "answer": "apply to the court to punish the criminal"
  },
  {
    "question": "A three-tier trial system in South Korea is ___ conducted.",
    "options": [
      "District Court",
      "High Court",
      "Supreme Court",
      "Constitutional Court"
    ],
    "answer": "Supreme Court"
  },
  {
    "question": "The role of the officials at the immigration office or customs is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "to directly investigate instead of the police",
      "to demand punishment for criminals",
      "to file a case in court",
      "to direct investigations"
    ],
    "answer": "to directly investigate instead of the police"
  },
  {
    "question": "The minimum age to get married in Korea is ___ years old.",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "18",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, A situation where one cannot proceed with a divorce without agreement is ___.",
    "options": [
      "when the other party abuses the children",
      "when the other party hides assets",
      "when the spouse does not fulfill their obligations",
      "when the other party is having an affair"
    ],
    "answer": "when the other party hides assets"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The law that protects people living on jeonse or monthly rent is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Housing Lease Protection Act",
      "Housing Lease Protection Rules",
      "Housing Lease Protection Ordinance",
      "Housing Lease Protection Guidelines"
    ],
    "answer": "Housing Lease Protection Act"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The usual duration of a lease contract is ___.",
    "options": [
      "1 year",
      "2 years",
      "3 years",
      "4 years"
    ],
    "answer": "2 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The party that does not raise the children after the divorce can meet the children ___",
    "options": [
      "within a limited scope is allowed",
      "cannot meet at all",
      "can meet freely",
      "depends on the decision of the family court"
    ],
    "answer": "within a limited scope is allowed"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, In order to conduct real estate transactions relatively safely, ___ is necessary.",
    "options": [
      "go through a certified broker",
      "go through a legal affairs agent",
      "go through a lawyer",
      "conduct the transaction directly"
    ],
    "answer": "go through a certified broker"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The law that protects people living on jeonse or monthly rent is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Housing Lease Protection Act",
      "Real Estate Protection Act",
      "Jeonse Protection Act",
      "Monthly Rent Protection Act"
    ],
    "answer": "Housing Lease Protection Act"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The typical duration of a lease agreement is ___.",
    "options": [
      "2 years",
      "1 year",
      "3 years",
      "5 years"
    ],
    "answer": "2 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, the place you need to report to be recognized as a couple is ___",
    "options": [
      "city hall, district office, county office",
      "police station, fire station",
      "hospital, pharmacy",
      "school, library"
    ],
    "answer": "city hall, district office, county office"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, Couples cannot refuse ___ for no special reason.",
    "options": [
      "to live together",
      "to eat together",
      "to travel together",
      "to work together"
    ],
    "answer": "to live together"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, When a couple wants to end their relationship, the way to divorce is ___.",
    "options": [
      "by agreement or trial",
      "by agreement or mediation",
      "by agreement or adjustment",
      "by agreement or negotiation"
    ],
    "answer": "by agreement or trial"
  },
  {
    "question": "The spouse who caused the divorce and is at fault must ____ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "pay alimony to the other party",
      "pay child support",
      "divide the property",
      "bear all the divorce costs"
    ],
    "answer": "pay alimony to the other party"
  },
  {
    "question": "The party entrusted with raising the child can demand ____ from the other party in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Costs necessary for child-rearing",
      "Divorce expenses",
      "Alimony",
      "Part of the property"
    ],
    "answer": "Costs necessary for child-rearing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Even if parents divorce, the relationship between parents and children in Korea is ___",
    "options": [
      "maintained as is",
      "severed",
      "determined by the court",
      "determined by the child's will"
    ],
    "answer": "maintained as is"
  },
  {
    "question": "When having difficulty finding a lawyer, in Korea, you can get help from ___",
    "options": [
      "the government",
      "foreign embassies",
      "the Legal Aid Corporation",
      "personal connections"
    ],
    "answer": "the Legal Aid Corporation"
  },
  {
    "question": "A service that is not provided by the Korea Legal Aid Corporation is ___.",
    "options": [
      "legal consultation",
      "litigation representation",
      "Korean language education",
      "foreign language education"
    ],
    "answer": "foreign language education"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The most desirable method for resolving disputes is ___",
    "options": [
      "trial",
      "consultation with a lawyer",
      "dialogue and compromise between the parties",
      "protest to the government"
    ],
    "answer": "dialogue and compromise between the parties"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The main role of the National Human Rights Commission is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Protection of basic human rights",
      "Providing legal advice",
      "Protection of consumer rights",
      "Assistance to foreigners"
    ],
    "answer": "Protection of basic human rights"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main role of the Korea Consumer Agency is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Protection of basic human rights",
      "Providing legal advice",
      "Activities to protect consumer rights",
      "Support for foreigners"
    ],
    "answer": "Activities to protect consumer rights"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a consumer who has suffered damage informs about the damage In Korea, the place where they can receive consultation or remedy is ___",
    "options": [
      "Korea Consumer Agency",
      "National Human Rights Commission",
      "Community Center",
      "Foreigners Support Center"
    ],
    "answer": "Korea Consumer Agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "When faced with legal issues, to alleviate difficulties and prevent legal disputes in advance, the institution that provides legal information in Korea is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Korea National Police Agency",
      "Ministry of Justice",
      "National Assembly",
      "Supreme Court"
    ],
    "answer": "Ministry of Justice"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Korea, The location of the Statue of Justice is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Supreme Court, Seocho-dong, Seocho-gu, Seoul",
      "Supreme Court, Jongno-gu, Seoul",
      "Supreme Court, Gangnam-gu, Seoul",
      "Supreme Court, Jung-gu, Seoul"
    ],
    "answer": "Supreme Court, Seocho-dong, Seocho-gu, Seoul"
  },
  {
    "question": "The essential advisory body under the constitution for responding to the president's consultations is ___ in Korea.",
    "options": [
      "Council of National Advisors",
      "Democratic Peace and Unification Advisory Council",
      "National Security Council",
      "National Economic Advisory Council"
    ],
    "answer": "National Security Council"
  }
]